{"id": "B00009W44W", "docid": "B00009W44W", "token": ["This", "Dormont", "gas", "connector", "is", "CSA", "Design", "Certified", "domestically", "and", "internationally", "for", "indoor", "and", "outdoor", "use", "with", "natural", ",", "manufactured", ",", "mixed", ",", "liquefied", "petroleum", ",", "and", "LP", "-", "gas", "air", "mixtures", "Durable", ",", "naturally", "corrosion", "-", "resistant", "304", "stainless", "steel", "construction", "offers", "an", "exclusive", "no", "-", "neck", "design", "to", "increase", "flexibility", "Quality", "flared", "end", "fittings", "create", "a", "metal", "to", "metal", "seal", "to", "ensure", "integrity", "in", "critical", "applications", "Manufactured", "domestically", "in", "the", "USA", ",", "all", "Dormont", "gas", "connectors", "are", "100", "percent", "leak", "tested", "to", "ensure", "consistent", "quality", "you", "can", "trust", "."], "ner": ["O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-CARDINAL", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ENERGY_EFFICIENCY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-GPE", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERCENT", "I-PERCENT", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "pos": ["DET", "PROPN", "NOUN", "NOUN", "VERB", "PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "ADV", "CCONJ", "ADV", "ADP", "ADJ", "CCONJ", "ADJ", "NOUN", "ADP", "ADJ", "PUNCT", "VERB", "PUNCT", "ADJ", "PUNCT", "VERB", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "NOUN", "NOUN", "ADJ", "PUNCT", "ADV", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "ADJ", "NUM", "ADJ", "NOUN", "NOUN", "VERB", "DET", "ADJ", "DET", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "NOUN", "PART", "VERB", "NOUN", "NOUN", "VERB", "NOUN", "NOUN", "VERB", "DET", "NOUN", "ADP", "NOUN", "NOUN", "PART", "VERB", "NOUN", "ADP", "ADJ", "NOUN", "VERB", "ADV", "ADP", "DET", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "DET", "PROPN", "NOUN", "NOUN", "VERB", "NUM", "NOUN", "NOUN", "VERB", "PART", "VERB", "ADJ", "NOUN", "PRON", "VERB", "VERB", "PUNCT"], "dep_head": [3, 3, 3, 4, 42, 7, 7, 4, 4, 8, 8, 4, 15, 12, 12, 11, 15, 24, 17, 17, 19, 19, 21, 24, 16, 24, 24, 29, 29, 30, 31, 24, 31, 42, 37, 37, 37, 41, 41, 40, 41, 42, 78, 48, 48, 47, 47, 48, 42, 50, 48, 50, 55, 54, 55, 56, 42, 58, 56, 58, 61, 59, 63, 56, 63, 64, 67, 65, 63, 68, 68, 72, 70, 78, 77, 77, 77, 78, 78, 80, 81, 78, 81, 84, 82, 86, 84, 89, 89, 86, 78], "dep_rel": ["det", "compound", "compound", "nsubj", "ccomp", "compound", "compound", "attr", "advmod", "cc", "conj", "prep", "amod", "cc", "conj", "pobj", "prep", "amod", "punct", "conj", "punct", "conj", "punct", "amod", "pobj", "punct", "cc", "compound", "punct", "compound", "compound", "conj", "amod", "punct", "advmod", "npadvmod", "punct", "amod", "nummod", "amod", "compound", "nsubj", "ccomp", "det", "amod", "det", "punct", "compound", "dobj", "aux", "relcl", "dobj", "nmod", "amod", "compound", "nsubj", "conj", "det", "dobj", "prep", "compound", "pobj", "aux", "advcl", "dobj", "prep", "amod", "pobj", "advcl", "advmod", "prep", "det", "pobj", "punct", "det", "compound", "compound", "nsubj", "ROOT", "nummod", "compound", "attr", "acl", "aux", "advcl", "amod", "dobj", "nsubj", "aux", "relcl", "punct"]}
{"id": "B00009YWJX", "docid": "B00009YWJX", "token": ["The", "revolutionary", "EQUATOR", "EZ", "3612", "CEE", "is", "an", "amazing", "combination", "home", "appliance", "that", "actually", "washes", "and", "dries", "clothing", "in", "one", "machine", "!", "Combining", "these", "functions", "saves", "you", "time", ",", "space", ",", "work", ",", "energy", "and", "money", ".", "Simply", "put", "in", "laundry", ",", "choose", "settings", "and", "press", "\"", "Start", "\"", ".", "You", "will", "return", "to", "clean", ",", "dry", "clothes", "-", "ready", "to", "fold", "and", "put", "away", "!", " ", "Hot", "air", "used", "in", "drying", "is", "water", "cooled", "internally", "-", "condensation", "flushed", "by", "water", "pump", "   ", "Wash", "or", "Dry", "option", "   ", "3", "Wash", "/", "Rinse", "settings", "   ", "Half", "load", "option", "   ", "Auto", "additive", "dispenser", "   ", "Heat", "-", " ", "650", "/", "1300", "Watts", "   ", "Dry", "Time", "-", " ", "0", "-", "120", "minutes", "   ", "Standard", "115V", "-", "60Hz", "-", "12.8", "amps", "power", "requirements", "   ", "Dimensions", "-", " ", "33H", "x", "24W", "x", "23", "-", "1/2D", ";", "weighs", "176", "pounds", "   ", "1", "Year", "Limited", "P&L", ";", "Warranty"], "ner": ["O", "O", "B-PRODUCT", "I-PRODUCT", "I-PRODUCT", "I-PRODUCT", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-CARDINAL", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-WORK_OF_ART", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-CARDINAL", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "B-CARDINAL", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-CARDINAL", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "B-TIME", "I-TIME", "I-TIME", "I-TIME", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-CARDINAL", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-QUANTITY", "I-QUANTITY", "O", "B-DATE", "I-DATE", "O", "O", "O", "B-CARDINAL"], "pos": ["DET", "ADJ", "PROPN", "PROPN", "NUM", "PROPN", "VERB", "DET", "ADJ", "NOUN", "NOUN", "NOUN", "DET", "ADV", "VERB", "CCONJ", "VERB", "NOUN", "ADP", "NUM", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "VERB", "DET", "NOUN", "VERB", "PRON", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "CCONJ", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "ADV", "VERB", "PART", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "VERB", "NOUN", "CCONJ", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "PUNCT", "PRON", "VERB", "VERB", "ADP", "VERB", "PUNCT", "ADJ", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "ADJ", "PART", "VERB", "CCONJ", "VERB", "ADV", "PUNCT", "SPACE", "ADJ", "NOUN", "VERB", "ADP", "NOUN", "VERB", "NOUN", "VERB", "ADV", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "VERB", "ADP", "NOUN", "NOUN", "SPACE", "PROPN", "CCONJ", "ADJ", "NOUN", "SPACE", "NUM", "PROPN", "SYM", "PROPN", "NOUN", "SPACE", "ADJ", "NOUN", "NOUN", "SPACE", "NOUN", "NOUN", "NOUN", "SPACE", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "SPACE", "NUM", "SYM", "NUM", "PROPN", "SPACE", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "SPACE", "NUM", "SYM", "NUM", "NOUN", "SPACE", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "NUM", "PUNCT", "NUM", "NOUN", "NOUN", "NOUN", "SPACE", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "SPACE", "NUM", "SYM", "NUM", "SYM", "NUM", "SYM", "NUM", "PUNCT", "VERB", "NUM", "NOUN", "SPACE", "NUM", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "NOUN"], "dep_head": [5, 3, 3, 5, 5, 6, 6, 11, 11, 11, 11, 6, 14, 14, 11, 14, 14, 16, 16, 20, 18, 6, 25, 24, 22, 25, 25, 25, 27, 27, 29, 29, 31, 31, 33, 33, 25, 38, 38, 38, 38, 38, 38, 42, 43, 43, 47, 42, 47, 38, 52, 52, 52, 52, 59, 59, 59, 59, 59, 53, 61, 59, 61, 61, 63, 52, 65, 68, 72, 68, 69, 70, 72, 74, 72, 77, 77, 74, 77, 78, 81, 86, 81, 86, 83, 83, 79, 86, 92, 91, 91, 92, 74, 92, 96, 96, 96, 96, 100, 100, 100, 100, 100, 102, 103, 107, 107, 108, 108, 108, 111, 108, 111, 112, 116, 116, 117, 117, 117, 124, 124, 124, 124, 124, 125, 127, 127, 127, 127, 129, 129, 130, 138, 138, 133, 138, 135, 138, 139, 140, 140, 142, 140, 142, 145, 147, 147, 147, 147, 148], "dep_rel": ["det", "amod", "nmod", "nmod", "nummod", "nsubj", "ROOT", "det", "amod", "compound", "compound", "attr", "nsubj", "advmod", "relcl", "cc", "conj", "dobj", "prep", "nummod", "pobj", "punct", "csubj", "det", "dobj", "ROOT", "dative", "dobj", "punct", "conj", "punct", "conj", "punct", "conj", "cc", "conj", "punct", "advmod", "ROOT", "prt", "dobj", "punct", "dep", "dobj", "cc", "conj", "punct", "xcomp", "punct", "punct", "nsubj", "aux", "ROOT", "prep", "amod", "punct", "amod", "npadvmod", "punct", "pobj", "aux", "xcomp", "cc", "conj", "advmod", "punct", "", "amod", "nsubj", "acl", "prep", "pobj", "ROOT", "nsubj", "ccomp", "amod", "punct", "dobj", "acl", "agent", "compound", "nmod", "", "nmod", "cc", "conj", "pobj", "", "nummod", "nmod", "punct", "compound", "dep", "", "nmod", "compound", "ROOT", "", "compound", "compound", "ROOT", "", "appos", "punct", "", "quantmod", "punct", "nummod", "ROOT", "", "compound", "appos", "punct", "", "quantmod", "punct", "nummod", "ROOT", "", "quantmod", "quantmod", "punct", "quantmod", "punct", "nummod", "compound", "compound", "ROOT", "", "ROOT", "punct", "", "nummod", "punct", "pobj", "punct", "pobj", "punct", "punct", "punct", "ROOT", "nummod", "nsubj", "", "nummod", "compound", "compound", "ROOT", "punct", "pobj"]}
{"id": "B0000AYKNU", "docid": "B0000AYKNU", "token": ["Haier", "'s", "Portable", "8.8", "lbs", ".", "Capacity", "Pulsator", "Washing", "System"], "ner": ["B-BRAND", "O", "O", "B-QUANTITY", "I-QUANTITY", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"], "pos": ["PROPN", "PART", "PROPN", "NUM", "ADV", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "NOUN"], "dep_head": [4, 0, 4, 4, 4, 4, 9, 8, 9, 9], "dep_rel": ["poss", "case", "amod", "nummod", "ROOT", "punct", "compound", "compound", "compound", "ROOT"]}
{"id": "B0000AYKNT", "docid": "B0000AYKNT", "token": ["Haier", "'s", "Portable", "Pulsator", "Washing", "System", "with", "SS", "Tub"], "ner": ["B-BRAND", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O"], "pos": ["PROPN", "PART", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN"], "dep_head": [5, 0, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 8, 6], "dep_rel": ["poss", "case", "compound", "compound", "compound", "ROOT", "prep", "compound", "pobj"]}
{"id": "B000195ZKU", "docid": "B000195ZKU", "token": ["Quiet", ",", "versatile", "and", "energy", "efficient", ",", "this", "front", "-", "loading", "washer", "from", "the", "Haier", "family", "of", "appliances", "has", "an", "11-lb", ".", "capacity", "and", "a", "1.5", "cu", ".", "ft", ".", "stainless", "steel", "drum", ".", "Choose", "from", "8", "fabric", "care", "wash", "cycles", "and", "other", "options", "like", "water", "-", "saving", "rinse", "and", "spin", "cycle", "on", "/", "off", ".", "Other", "features", "include", "auto", "select", "wash", "/", "rinse", "temperature", ";", "adjustable", "leveling", "legs", "and", "retractable", "casters", ";", "and", "detergent", "and", "fabric", "softener", "dispenser", ".", "Use", "it", "built", "in", "or", "freestanding", ".", "Can", "be", "stacked", "with", "the", "Haier", "11", "lb", ".", "Front", "Loading", "Dryer", "using", "the", "Stacking", "Kit", "(", "each", "sold", "separately", ")", ".", "Haier", "Customer", "Service", "is", "available", "8am-5pm", "CST", ",", "Monday", "thru", "Friday", "via", "JMA", "&", "Associates", "at", "1", "-", "952", "-", "469", "-", "2155", "phone", ",", "1", "-", "952", "-", "469", "-", "3655", "fax", "or", "e", "-", "mail", "to", "jmacs@frontiernet.net", ".", "Imported", ".", "34Hx24Wx22D", "\"", ".", "Shipping", "weight", ":", "172", "lbs", ".", "Curbside", "delivery", "only", ".", "This", "is", "an", "oversized", "item", "and", "requires", "special", "handling", ".", "This", "item", "will", "ship", "separately", "from", "other", "items", ".", "An", "additonal", "flat", "fee", "will", "be", "added", "at", "checkout", ".", "Once", "the", "order", "leaves", "the", "distribution", "center", ",", "you", "will", "be", "contacted", "by", "the", "shipper", "to", "arrange", "a", "specific", "time", "for", "delivery", ".", "Guest", "should", "be", "present", "at", "the", "time", "of", "delivery", "and", "will", "be", "responsible", "for", "getting", "the", "item", "inside", "."], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-BRAND", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ENERGY_EFFICIENCY", "B-QUANTITY", "I-QUANTITY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-CARDINAL", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-BRAND", "B-QUANTITY", "I-QUANTITY", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-PRODUCT", "I-PRODUCT", "I-PRODUCT", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-BRAND", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-DATE", "B-ORG", "O", "B-DATE", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-CARDINAL", "I-CARDINAL", "I-CARDINAL", "I-CARDINAL", "I-CARDINAL", "I-CARDINAL", "I-CARDINAL", "O", "O", "B-CARDINAL", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ENERGY_EFFICIENCY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-QUANTITY", "I-QUANTITY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ENERGY_EFFICIENCY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "pos": ["ADJ", "PUNCT", "ADJ", "CCONJ", "NOUN", "ADJ", "PUNCT", "DET", "ADJ", "PUNCT", "VERB", "NOUN", "ADP", "DET", "PROPN", "NOUN", "ADP", "NOUN", "VERB", "DET", "NUM", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "CCONJ", "DET", "NUM", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "ADJ", "NOUN", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "VERB", "ADP", "NUM", "NOUN", "NOUN", "NOUN", "NOUN", "CCONJ", "ADJ", "NOUN", "ADP", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "NOUN", "CCONJ", "VERB", "NOUN", "ADP", "SYM", "ADV", "PUNCT", "ADJ", "NOUN", "VERB", "NOUN", "NOUN", "NOUN", "SYM", "NOUN", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "ADJ", "NOUN", "NOUN", "CCONJ", "ADJ", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "CCONJ", "NOUN", "CCONJ", "NOUN", "NOUN", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "VERB", "PRON", "VERB", "ADP", "CCONJ", "ADJ", "PUNCT", "VERB", "VERB", "VERB", "ADP", "DET", "PROPN", "NUM", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "DET", "PROPN", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "DET", "VERB", "ADV", "PUNCT", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "ADJ", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "ADP", "NUM", "SYM", "NUM", "PUNCT", "NUM", "PUNCT", "NUM", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "NUM", "SYM", "NUM", "PUNCT", "NUM", "PUNCT", "NUM", "NOUN", "CCONJ", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "ADP", "X", "PUNCT", "VERB", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "NUM", "ADP", "PUNCT", "ADJ", "NOUN", "ADV", "PUNCT", "DET", "VERB", "DET", "ADJ", "NOUN", "CCONJ", "VERB", "ADJ", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "DET", "NOUN", "VERB", "VERB", "ADV", "ADP", "ADJ", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "DET", "ADJ", "ADJ", "NOUN", "VERB", "VERB", "VERB", "ADP", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "ADP", "DET", "NOUN", "VERB", "DET", "NOUN", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "PRON", "VERB", "VERB", "VERB", "ADP", "DET", "NOUN", "PART", "VERB", "DET", "ADJ", "NOUN", "ADP", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "VERB", "VERB", "ADJ", "ADP", "DET", "NOUN", "ADP", "NOUN", "CCONJ", "VERB", "VERB", "ADJ", "ADP", "VERB", "DET", "NOUN", "ADV", "PUNCT"], "dep_head": [5, 0, 0, 2, 2, 18, 18, 11, 10, 10, 11, 18, 11, 15, 15, 12, 15, 16, 18, 20, 18, 18, 22, 22, 32, 26, 24, 26, 32, 32, 32, 32, 22, 22, 34, 34, 40, 38, 39, 40, 35, 40, 43, 40, 40, 47, 47, 48, 51, 48, 48, 44, 34, 52, 52, 34, 57, 58, 58, 64, 64, 63, 63, 64, 58, 64, 67, 68, 64, 68, 71, 68, 68, 68, 78, 74, 74, 78, 68, 58, 80, 82, 80, 82, 82, 82, 80, 89, 89, 89, 89, 94, 94, 94, 90, 89, 98, 98, 98, 98, 102, 102, 99, 98, 98, 104, 105, 98, 98, 111, 111, 112, 145, 112, 115, 113, 115, 112, 117, 118, 112, 120, 121, 121, 112, 131, 127, 131, 131, 131, 131, 132, 124, 145, 140, 136, 140, 140, 140, 140, 145, 145, 141, 145, 145, 145, 145, 146, 145, 149, 149, 151, 151, 151, 154, 154, 157, 158, 154, 154, 161, 161, 161, 161, 165, 165, 168, 168, 165, 165, 165, 172, 170, 165, 175, 177, 177, 177, 177, 177, 181, 179, 177, 186, 186, 186, 189, 189, 189, 189, 189, 190, 189, 196, 195, 196, 204, 199, 199, 196, 204, 204, 204, 204, 204, 204, 207, 205, 209, 204, 212, 212, 209, 212, 213, 204, 218, 218, 218, 218, 218, 222, 220, 222, 223, 218, 227, 218, 227, 228, 229, 232, 230, 232, 218], "dep_rel": ["amod", "punct", "conj", "cc", "conj", "ccomp", "punct", "det", "npadvmod", "punct", "amod", "nsubj", "prep", "det", "compound", "pobj", "prep", "pobj", "ROOT", "det", "dobj", "punct", "ROOT", "cc", "det", "nummod", "pobj", "punct", "intj", "punct", "amod", "compound", "conj", "punct", "ROOT", "prep", "nummod", "compound", "compound", "compound", "pobj", "cc", "amod", "conj", "prep", "npadvmod", "punct", "amod", "nmod", "cc", "conj", "pobj", "prep", "punct", "pobj", "punct", "amod", "nsubj", "ROOT", "nmod", "amod", "nmod", "punct", "compound", "dobj", "punct", "amod", "compound", "conj", "cc", "amod", "conj", "punct", "cc", "nmod", "cc", "conj", "compound", "conj", "punct", "ROOT", "nsubj", "ccomp", "prep", "cc", "conj", "punct", "aux", "auxpass", "ROOT", "prep", "det", "nmod", "nummod", "pobj", "punct", "compound", "compound", "ROOT", "acl", "det", "compound", "dobj", "punct", "appos", "acl", "advmod", "punct", "punct", "compound", "compound", "nsubj", "ccomp", "acomp", "nummod", "dobj", "punct", "npadvmod", "prep", "pobj", "prep", "pobj", "cc", "conj", "prep", "quantmod", "punct", "quantmod", "punct", "nummod", "punct", "nummod", "pobj", "punct", "quantmod", "punct", "nummod", "punct", "nummod", "punct", "nummod", "nmod", "cc", "compound", "punct", "ROOT", "prep", "pobj", "punct", "ROOT", "punct", "ROOT", "punct", "punct", "ROOT", "dobj", "punct", "nummod", "npadvmod", "punct", "compound", "ROOT", "advmod", "punct", "nsubj", "ROOT", "det", "amod", "attr", "cc", "conj", "amod", "dobj", "punct", "det", "nsubj", "aux", "ROOT", "advmod", "prep", "amod", "pobj", "punct", "det", "amod", "amod", "nsubjpass", "aux", "auxpass", "ROOT", "prep", "pobj", "punct", "advmod", "det", "nsubj", "advcl", "det", "compound", "dobj", "punct", "nsubjpass", "aux", "auxpass", "ROOT", "agent", "det", "pobj", "aux", "advcl", "det", "amod", "dobj", "prep", "pobj", "punct", "nsubj", "aux", "ROOT", "acomp", "prep", "det", "pobj", "prep", "pobj", "cc", "aux", "conj", "acomp", "prep", "pcomp", "det", "dobj", "advmod", "punct"]}
{"id": "B0002KXMT4", "docid": "B0002KXMT4", "token": ["Haier", "'s", "1.0", "cu", ".", "ft", ".", "compact", "Pulsator", "Washer", "provides", "the", "convenience", "of", "at", "-", "home", "laundry", "facilities", "for", "spaces", "where", "full", "-", "size", "machines", "are", "not", "an", "option", ".", "It", "is", "ideal", "for", "small", "apartments", ",", "mobile", "homes", ",", "and", "other", "places", "where", "space", "is", "limited", ".", "This", "model", "features", "a", "durable", "stainless", "steel", "tub", "and", "gives", "you", "a", "choice", "of", "Heavy", ",", "Normal", ",", "or", "Quick", "Wash", "cycles", "and", "Low", ",", "Medium", ",", "or", "High", "water", "levels", "for", "the", "perfect", "combination", "every", "time", ".", "The", "unit", "plugs", "into", "any", "standard", "household", "120-Volt", "outlet", "and", "connects", "quickly", "and", "easily", "to", "any", "sink", ".", "Get", "the", "best", "fit", "with", "the", "included", "fill", "and", "drain", "hoses", "and", "Quick", "-", "Connect", "sink", "adapter", ".", "It", "also", "offers", "optimum", "portability", "since", "it", "can", "be", "easily", "rolled", "away", "for", "storage", ".", "All", "this", "plus", "quiet", "operation", "adds", "up", "to", "the", "ultimate", "in", "compact", "laundry", "solutions", ".", "Small", "Yet", "PowerfulThis", "easy", "-", "to", "-", "use", ",", "compact", "washer", "features", "a", "durable", "stainless", "steel", "tub", "and", "uses", "a", "pulsator", "system", "rather", "than", "a", "traditional", "agitator", "to", "create", "a", "powerful", "and", "effective", "wash", "action", "without", "the", "twisting", "and", "pulling", "that", "an", "agitator", "can", "cause", ".", "The", "absence", "of", "an", "agitator", "also", "frees", "up", "additional", "space", "in", "the", "wash", "tub", "to", "provide", "you", "with", "maximum", "wash", "load", "capacity", ".", "The", "pulsating", "action", "results", "in", "superb", "cleaning", "performance", "in", "a", "non", "-", "abrasive", "wash", "environment", ".", "It", "is", "gentler", "on", "clothes", "as", "well", ",", "making", "it", "excellent", "for", "items", "such", "as", "cloth", "diapers", ",", "baby", "clothes", ",", "and", "delicate", ".", "Digital", "ControlsChoose", "from", "Heavy", ",", "Normal", ",", "or", "Quick", "Wash", "cycles", "and", "Low", ",", "Medium", ",", "or", "High", "electronically", "controlled", "water", "levels", "on", "a", "simple", "touch", "pad", "to", "get", "the", "perfect", "combination", "for", "your", "load", "every", "time", ".", "The", "electronic", "controls", "include", "a", "pause", "button", "should", "you", "need", "to", "interrupt", "the", "cycle", "for", "any", "reason", ",", "and", "a", "clear", "viewing", "window", "at", "the", "top", "lets", "you", "check", "on", "your", "laundry", ".", "LED", "indicator", "lights", "clearly", "display", "the", "cycle", "status", ",", "and", "an", "end", "-", "of", "-", "cycle", "signal", "alerts", "you", "when", "clothes", "are", "clean", "and", "ready", "to", "be", "removed", ".", "Easy", ",", "No", "-", "Fuss", "InstallationThis", "compact", "washer", "doesn&rsquo;t", "just", "fit", "into", "small", "spaces", ";", "it", "connects", "quickly", "and", "easily", "to", "any", "sink", ".", "Get", "the", "best", "fit", "with", "the", "included", "fill", "and", "drain", "hoses", "and", "Quick", "Connect", "sink", "adapter", ".", "Because", "the", "unit", "plugs", "into", "any", "standard", "household", "120-Volt", "outlet", "it", "can", "be", "used", "virtually", "anywhere", "in", "your", "living", "space&mdash;no", "need", "for", "specialized", "or", "complicated", "electrical", "connections", ".", "All", "this", "plus", "outstanding", "portability", "adds", "up", "to", "the", "ultimate", "in", "compact", "laundry", "solutions", "."], "ner": ["B-BRAND", "O", "B-QUANTITY", "I-QUANTITY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PRODUCT", "I-PRODUCT", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ENERGY_EFFICIENCY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ENERGY_EFFICIENCY", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-CARDINAL", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ENERGY_EFFICIENCY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ENERGY_EFFICIENCY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ENERGY_EFFICIENCY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ENERGY_EFFICIENCY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ENERGY_EFFICIENCY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ENERGY_EFFICIENCY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ENERGY_EFFICIENCY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-BRAND", "O", "O", "B-ENERGY_EFFICIENCY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PRODUCT", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-CARDINAL", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "pos": ["PROPN", "PART", "NUM", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "ADJ", "PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "DET", "NOUN", "ADP", "ADP", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "NOUN", "NOUN", "ADP", "NOUN", "ADV", "ADJ", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "NOUN", "VERB", "ADV", "DET", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "PRON", "VERB", "ADJ", "ADP", "ADJ", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "ADJ", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "CCONJ", "ADJ", "NOUN", "ADV", "NOUN", "VERB", "VERB", "PUNCT", "DET", "NOUN", "VERB", "DET", "ADJ", "ADJ", "NOUN", "NOUN", "CCONJ", "VERB", "PRON", "DET", "NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "ADJ", "PUNCT", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PROPN", "NOUN", "CCONJ", "ADJ", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "CCONJ", "ADJ", "NOUN", "NOUN", "ADP", "DET", "ADJ", "NOUN", "DET", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "DET", "NOUN", "VERB", "ADP", "DET", "ADJ", "NOUN", "NUM", "NOUN", "CCONJ", "VERB", "ADV", "CCONJ", "ADV", "ADP", "DET", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "VERB", "DET", "ADJ", "NOUN", "ADP", "DET", "VERB", "NOUN", "CCONJ", "VERB", "NOUN", "CCONJ", "ADJ", "PUNCT", "VERB", "NOUN", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "PRON", "ADV", "VERB", "ADJ", "NOUN", "ADP", "PRON", "VERB", "VERB", "ADV", "VERB", "ADV", "ADP", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "DET", "DET", "CCONJ", "ADJ", "NOUN", "VERB", "PART", "ADP", "DET", "ADJ", "ADP", "ADJ", "ADJ", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "ADJ", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "ADJ", "PUNCT", "ADP", "PUNCT", "VERB", "PUNCT", "ADJ", "NOUN", "VERB", "DET", "ADJ", "ADJ", "NOUN", "NOUN", "CCONJ", "VERB", "DET", "NOUN", "NOUN", "ADV", "ADP", "DET", "ADJ", "NOUN", "PART", "VERB", "DET", "ADJ", "CCONJ", "ADJ", "NOUN", "NOUN", "ADP", "DET", "NOUN", "CCONJ", "VERB", "ADP", "DET", "NOUN", "VERB", "VERB", "PUNCT", "DET", "NOUN", "ADP", "DET", "NOUN", "ADV", "VERB", "PART", "ADJ", "NOUN", "ADP", "DET", "NOUN", "NOUN", "PART", "VERB", "PRON", "ADP", "ADJ", "NOUN", "NOUN", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "DET", "ADJ", "NOUN", "NOUN", "ADP", "ADJ", "NOUN", "NOUN", "ADP", "DET", "ADJ", "ADJ", "ADJ", "NOUN", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "PRON", "VERB", "ADJ", "ADP", "NOUN", "ADV", "ADV", "PUNCT", "VERB", "PRON", "ADJ", "ADP", "NOUN", "ADJ", "ADP", "NOUN", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "CCONJ", "ADJ", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "ADJ", "PUNCT", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PROPN", "NOUN", "CCONJ", "ADJ", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "CCONJ", "ADJ", "ADV", "VERB", "NOUN", "NOUN", "ADP", "DET", "ADJ", "NOUN", "NOUN", "PART", "VERB", "DET", "ADJ", "NOUN", "ADP", "DET", "NOUN", "DET", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "DET", "ADJ", "NOUN", "VERB", "DET", "NOUN", "NOUN", "VERB", "PRON", "VERB", "PART", "VERB", "DET", "NOUN", "ADP", "DET", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "CCONJ", "DET", "ADJ", "VERB", "NOUN", "ADP", "DET", "NOUN", "VERB", "PRON", "VERB", "ADP", "DET", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "VERB", "NOUN", "NOUN", "ADV", "VERB", "DET", "NOUN", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "CCONJ", "DET", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "ADP", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "NOUN", "VERB", "PRON", "ADV", "NOUN", "VERB", "ADJ", "CCONJ", "ADJ", "PART", "VERB", "VERB", "PUNCT", "ADV", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "PROPN", "ADJ", "NOUN", "ADV", "ADV", "VERB", "ADP", "ADJ", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "PRON", "VERB", "ADV", "CCONJ", "ADV", "ADP", "DET", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "VERB", "DET", "ADJ", "NOUN", "ADP", "DET", "VERB", "NOUN", "CCONJ", "VERB", "NOUN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PROPN", "NOUN", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "ADP", "DET", "NOUN", "VERB", "ADP", "DET", "ADJ", "NOUN", "NUM", "NOUN", "PRON", "VERB", "VERB", "VERB", "ADV", "ADV", "ADP", "DET", "VERB", "PRON", "NOUN", "ADP", "ADJ", "CCONJ", "ADJ", "ADJ", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "DET", "DET", "CCONJ", "ADJ", "NOUN", "VERB", "PART", "ADP", "DET", "ADJ", "ADP", "ADJ", "ADJ", "NOUN", "PUNCT"], "dep_head": [9, 0, 3, 0, 3, 6, 0, 9, 9, 10, 10, 12, 10, 12, 18, 14, 14, 18, 13, 10, 19, 26, 24, 24, 25, 26, 20, 26, 29, 26, 10, 32, 32, 32, 32, 36, 34, 36, 39, 36, 39, 39, 43, 39, 46, 46, 43, 46, 32, 50, 51, 51, 56, 56, 56, 56, 51, 51, 51, 58, 61, 58, 61, 70, 63, 63, 65, 65, 69, 65, 62, 70, 70, 72, 72, 74, 74, 79, 79, 70, 79, 83, 83, 80, 85, 58, 51, 88, 89, 89, 89, 95, 95, 94, 95, 90, 89, 89, 97, 98, 98, 97, 103, 101, 89, 105, 108, 108, 105, 108, 112, 112, 109, 112, 112, 114, 115, 119, 119, 115, 121, 112, 105, 125, 125, 125, 127, 125, 133, 133, 133, 133, 133, 125, 133, 133, 135, 125, 142, 142, 139, 142, 143, 143, 143, 143, 147, 145, 147, 151, 151, 148, 143, 153, 155, 163, 163, 156, 156, 158, 158, 163, 163, 164, 164, 169, 169, 169, 169, 164, 164, 164, 174, 174, 171, 176, 174, 179, 179, 174, 181, 179, 187, 187, 183, 183, 187, 181, 181, 190, 188, 181, 181, 197, 195, 197, 197, 171, 164, 200, 205, 200, 203, 201, 205, 205, 205, 208, 205, 205, 212, 212, 209, 214, 205, 214, 214, 220, 219, 220, 216, 205, 225, 225, 225, 225, 225, 229, 229, 226, 229, 236, 233, 234, 236, 236, 230, 225, 239, 239, 239, 239, 241, 244, 239, 239, 239, 248, 246, 248, 249, 252, 250, 254, 252, 254, 257, 254, 257, 257, 257, 239, 263, 263, 263, 272, 265, 265, 267, 267, 271, 267, 264, 272, 272, 274, 274, 276, 276, 283, 281, 283, 283, 276, 263, 288, 288, 288, 284, 290, 263, 293, 293, 290, 293, 296, 294, 298, 290, 263, 302, 302, 303, 303, 306, 306, 303, 309, 309, 309, 311, 309, 313, 311, 311, 316, 314, 309, 309, 322, 322, 322, 326, 322, 325, 323, 309, 328, 326, 328, 331, 329, 309, 335, 335, 337, 337, 337, 340, 340, 337, 337, 337, 350, 349, 344, 344, 346, 346, 350, 337, 350, 354, 354, 350, 354, 355, 355, 360, 360, 357, 350, 378, 370, 367, 366, 367, 370, 369, 370, 372, 372, 378, 372, 375, 373, 378, 378, 378, 378, 379, 379, 378, 384, 382, 378, 386, 389, 389, 386, 389, 393, 393, 390, 393, 393, 395, 389, 399, 389, 386, 400, 386, 406, 405, 406, 416, 406, 412, 412, 411, 412, 407, 416, 416, 416, 416, 418, 416, 418, 422, 422, 419, 416, 423, 429, 425, 425, 429, 424, 416, 432, 436, 432, 435, 432, 436, 436, 436, 440, 438, 440, 444, 444, 441, 436], "dep_rel": ["nmod", "case", "nummod", "pobj", "punct", "subtok", "punct", "amod", "compound", "nsubj", "ROOT", "det", "dobj", "prep", "nmod", "punct", "pobj", "compound", "pobj", "prep", "pobj", "advmod", "amod", "punct", "compound", "nsubj", "relcl", "neg", "det", "attr", "punct", "nsubj", "ROOT", "acomp", "prep", "amod", "pobj", "punct", "amod", "conj", "punct", "cc", "amod", "conj", "advmod", "nsubj", "relcl", "acomp", "punct", "det", "nsubj", "ROOT", "det", "amod", "amod", "compound", "dobj", "cc", "conj", "dative", "det", "dobj", "prep", "amod", "punct", "conj", "punct", "cc", "compound", "conj", "pobj", "cc", "conj", "punct", "conj", "punct", "cc", "amod", "compound", "conj", "prep", "det", "amod", "pobj", "det", "npadvmod", "punct", "det", "nsubj", "ROOT", "prep", "det", "amod", "compound", "compound", "pobj", "cc", "conj", "advmod", "cc", "conj", "prep", "det", "pobj", "punct", "ROOT", "det", "amod", "dobj", "prep", "det", "amod", "pobj", "cc", "conj", "dobj", "cc", "compound", "punct", "conj", "compound", "appos", "punct", "nsubj", "advmod", "ROOT", "amod", "dobj", "mark", "nsubjpass", "aux", "auxpass", "advmod", "advcl", "advmod", "prep", "pobj", "punct", "predet", "det", "cc", "amod", "nsubj", "ROOT", "prt", "prep", "det", "pobj", "prep", "amod", "compound", "pobj", "punct", "ROOT", "compound", "amod", "amod", "punct", "prep", "punct", "pobj", "punct", "amod", "nsubj", "ROOT", "det", "amod", "amod", "compound", "dobj", "cc", "conj", "det", "compound", "dobj", "advmod", "cc", "det", "amod", "conj", "aux", "relcl", "det", "amod", "cc", "conj", "compound", "dobj", "prep", "det", "pobj", "cc", "conj", "mark", "det", "nsubj", "aux", "advcl", "punct", "det", "nsubj", "prep", "det", "pobj", "advmod", "ROOT", "prt", "amod", "dobj", "prep", "det", "compound", "pobj", "aux", "advcl", "dobj", "prep", "amod", "compound", "compound", "pobj", "punct", "det", "amod", "compound", "ROOT", "prep", "amod", "compound", "pobj", "prep", "det", "subtok", "subtok", "amod", "compound", "pobj", "punct", "nsubj", "ROOT", "acomp", "prep", "pobj", "advmod", "advmod", "punct", "advcl", "nsubj", "ccomp", "prep", "pobj", "amod", "prep", "compound", "pobj", "punct", "compound", "conj", "punct", "cc", "conj", "punct", "compound", "ROOT", "prep", "nmod", "punct", "conj", "punct", "cc", "compound", "conj", "pobj", "cc", "conj", "punct", "conj", "punct", "cc", "amod", "advmod", "amod", "compound", "conj", "prep", "det", "amod", "compound", "pobj", "aux", "advcl", "det", "amod", "dobj", "prep", "poss", "pobj", "det", "npadvmod", "punct", "det", "amod", "nsubj", "ROOT", "det", "compound", "dobj", "aux", "nsubj", "ROOT", "aux", "xcomp", "det", "dobj", "prep", "det", "pobj", "punct", "cc", "det", "amod", "amod", "nsubj", "prep", "det", "pobj", "conj", "nsubj", "ccomp", "prep", "poss", "pobj", "punct", "compound", "compound", "nsubj", "advmod", "ROOT", "det", "compound", "dobj", "punct", "cc", "det", "nmod", "punct", "prep", "punct", "pobj", "compound", "conj", "dobj", "advmod", "nsubj", "advcl", "acomp", "cc", "conj", "aux", "auxpass", "xcomp", "punct", "advcl", "punct", "nmod", "punct", "compound", "nmod", "amod", "compound", "nsubj", "advmod", "ccomp", "prep", "amod", "pobj", "punct", "nsubj", "ROOT", "advmod", "cc", "conj", "prep", "det", "pobj", "punct", "ROOT", "det", "amod", "dobj", "prep", "det", "amod", "pobj", "cc", "conj", "dobj", "cc", "compound", "conj", "dep", "dobj", "punct", "mark", "det", "nsubj", "advcl", "prep", "det", "amod", "compound", "compound", "pobj", "nsubjpass", "aux", "auxpass", "ROOT", "advmod", "advmod", "prep", "poss", "amod", "pobj", "xcomp", "prep", "amod", "cc", "conj", "amod", "pobj", "punct", "predet", "nsubj", "cc", "amod", "conj", "ROOT", "prt", "prep", "det", "pobj", "prep", "amod", "compound", "pobj", "punct"]}
{"id": "B0002UDBRC", "docid": "B0002UDBRC", "token": ["The", "IQ", "-", "Touch", "controls", "on", "this", "front", "-", "load", "dryer", "make", "choosing", "a", "cycle", "easy", ".", "Pick", "from", "11", "cycles", "that", "provide", "proper", "care", "for", "clothing", ",", "towels", "and", "bedding", ".", "The", "Gentle", "Tumble", "dry", "system", "ensures", "gentle", ",", "even", "drying", "."], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ENERGY_EFFICIENCY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-CARDINAL", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "pos": ["DET", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "NOUN", "ADP", "DET", "ADJ", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "NOUN", "VERB", "VERB", "DET", "NOUN", "ADJ", "PUNCT", "VERB", "ADP", "NUM", "NOUN", "DET", "VERB", "ADJ", "NOUN", "ADP", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "CCONJ", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "DET", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADJ", "NOUN", "VERB", "ADJ", "PUNCT", "ADV", "VERB", "PUNCT"], "dep_head": [4, 3, 3, 4, 11, 4, 10, 9, 9, 10, 5, 11, 11, 14, 12, 12, 11, 17, 17, 20, 18, 22, 20, 24, 22, 24, 25, 26, 26, 28, 28, 17, 36, 34, 36, 36, 37, 37, 37, 37, 41, 37, 37], "dep_rel": ["det", "compound", "punct", "compound", "nsubj", "prep", "det", "amod", "punct", "compound", "pobj", "ROOT", "xcomp", "det", "dobj", "oprd", "punct", "ROOT", "prep", "nummod", "pobj", "nsubj", "relcl", "amod", "dobj", "prep", "pobj", "punct", "conj", "cc", "conj", "punct", "det", "nmod", "nmod", "amod", "nsubj", "ROOT", "acomp", "punct", "advmod", "advcl", "punct"]}
{"id": "B0007MEW14", "docid": "B0007MEW14", "token": ["The", "Koblenz", "space", "saving", "design", "of", "the", "LCK-50", "compact", "washing", "machine", "allows", "it", "to", "be", "stored", "almost", "anywhere", "in", "the", "home", ".", "Weighing", "only", "25.5", "pounds", ",", "it", "is", "easy", "to", "move", "from", "one", "place", "to", "another", ".", " ", "Features", "a", "rustproof", "polypropylene", "cabinet", "for", "longer", "life", "and", "a", "wide", "washtub", "opening", "for", "easy", "loading", "and", "unloading", ".", " ", "Washer", "controls", "are", "easy", "to", "use", "with", "a", "water", "level", "indicator", "and", "15", "minute", "automatic", "timer", ".", " ", "Includes", "a", "hose", "for", "the", "gravity", "drain", "feature", ".", "Machine", "agitates", "(", "does", "not", "spin", ")", "This", "great", "space", "saver", "can", "handle", "up", "to", "6.6", "pounds", "of", "laundry", "."], "ner": ["O", "B-GPE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-MONEY", "I-MONEY", "I-MONEY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-CARDINAL", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ENERGY_EFFICIENCY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ENERGY_EFFICIENCY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ENERGY_EFFICIENCY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TIME", "I-TIME", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ENERGY_EFFICIENCY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-QUANTITY", "I-QUANTITY", "O", "O", "O"], "pos": ["DET", "PROPN", "NOUN", "VERB", "NOUN", "ADP", "DET", "PROPN", "ADJ", "NOUN", "NOUN", "VERB", "PRON", "PART", "VERB", "VERB", "ADV", "ADV", "ADP", "DET", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "VERB", "ADV", "NUM", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "PRON", "VERB", "ADJ", "PART", "VERB", "ADP", "NUM", "NOUN", "ADP", "DET", "PUNCT", "SPACE", "VERB", "DET", "ADJ", "NOUN", "NOUN", "ADP", "ADJ", "NOUN", "CCONJ", "DET", "ADJ", "NOUN", "NOUN", "ADP", "ADJ", "NOUN", "CCONJ", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "SPACE", "PROPN", "NOUN", "VERB", "ADJ", "PART", "VERB", "ADP", "DET", "NOUN", "NOUN", "NOUN", "CCONJ", "NUM", "NOUN", "ADJ", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "SPACE", "VERB", "DET", "NOUN", "ADP", "DET", "NOUN", "NOUN", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "VERB", "PUNCT", "VERB", "ADV", "VERB", "PUNCT", "DET", "ADJ", "NOUN", "NOUN", "VERB", "VERB", "ADP", "PART", "NUM", "NOUN", "ADP", "NOUN", "PUNCT"], "dep_head": [4, 4, 3, 4, 11, 4, 10, 10, 9, 10, 5, 11, 15, 15, 15, 11, 17, 15, 17, 20, 18, 11, 28, 24, 25, 22, 28, 28, 28, 28, 31, 28, 31, 34, 32, 31, 35, 28, 37, 39, 43, 43, 43, 39, 39, 46, 44, 46, 51, 51, 51, 46, 51, 54, 52, 54, 54, 39, 57, 60, 61, 61, 61, 64, 62, 64, 69, 68, 69, 65, 69, 72, 74, 74, 69, 61, 75, 77, 79, 77, 79, 84, 83, 84, 80, 77, 87, 87, 91, 91, 91, 87, 91, 96, 96, 96, 98, 98, 98, 101, 101, 102, 98, 102, 103, 98], "dep_rel": ["det", "compound", "npadvmod", "compound", "nsubj", "prep", "det", "nmod", "amod", "compound", "pobj", "ROOT", "nsubjpass", "aux", "auxpass", "ccomp", "advmod", "advmod", "prep", "det", "pobj", "punct", "advcl", "advmod", "nummod", "dobj", "punct", "nsubj", "ROOT", "acomp", "aux", "xcomp", "prep", "nummod", "pobj", "prep", "pobj", "punct", "", "ROOT", "det", "amod", "compound", "dobj", "prep", "amod", "pobj", "cc", "det", "amod", "compound", "conj", "prep", "amod", "pobj", "cc", "conj", "punct", "", "compound", "nsubj", "ROOT", "acomp", "aux", "xcomp", "prep", "det", "compound", "compound", "pobj", "cc", "nummod", "nmod", "amod", "conj", "punct", "", "ROOT", "det", "dobj", "prep", "det", "compound", "compound", "pobj", "punct", "nsubj", "ROOT", "punct", "aux", "neg", "parataxis", "punct", "det", "amod", "compound", "nsubj", "aux", "ROOT", "quantmod", "quantmod", "nummod", "dobj", "prep", "pobj", "punct"]}
{"id": "B00092P6LC", "docid": "B00092P6LC", "token": ["Avanti", "W797", "Washer", "W797", "Portable", "Washer", "and", "Dryer"], "ner": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O"], "pos": ["PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN"], "dep_head": [2, 2, 3, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5], "dep_rel": ["compound", "subtok", "compound", "compound", "compound", "ROOT", "cc", "conj"]}
{"id": "B00097A4SW", "docid": "B00097A4SW", "token": ["White", "2.9", "cu.ft", "Capacity", "Energy", "Star(R", ")", "qualified", ",", "24&quot", ";", "Wide", "Front", "-", "Loading", "Washer"], "ner": ["O", "B-CARDINAL", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"], "pos": ["PROPN", "NUM", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "VERB", "PUNCT", "NUM", "PUNCT", "ADJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "NOUN"], "dep_head": [0, 0, 5, 5, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 15, 14, 14, 15, 0], "dep_rel": ["ROOT", "nummod", "compound", "compound", "compound", "conj", "punct", "amod", "punct", "appos", "punct", "compound", "compound", "punct", "compound", "appos"]}
{"id": "B0009JDL6C", "docid": "B0009JDL6C", "token": ["Our", "Shoe", "/", "Boot", "Dryer", "uses", "a", "mere", "36W", "for", "fan", "-", "free", ",", "silent", "convection", "of", "warmed", "air", "that", "dries", "all", "the", "way", "down", "to", "the", "toes", ".", " ", "Attach", "the", "optional", "Glove", "Attachment", "and", "safely", "dry", "your", "gloves", "overnight", ".", "   ", "Perfect", "for", "travel", "and", "vacations", ",", "our", " ", "Portable", "Dryer", "utilizes", "the", "same", "thermal", "convection", "technology", "in", "a", "compact", ",", "packable", "design", ";", "power", "adapter", "included", ".", "    ", "Size", " ", "10\"W", "x", "9", "-", "1/2\"D", "x", "22\"H"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ENERGY_EFFICIENCY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TIME", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ENERGY_EFFICIENCY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "B-CARDINAL", "O", "B-CARDINAL", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "pos": ["DET", "PROPN", "SYM", "PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "DET", "ADJ", "NUM", "ADP", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "ADJ", "PUNCT", "ADJ", "NOUN", "ADP", "VERB", "NOUN", "DET", "VERB", "DET", "DET", "NOUN", "PART", "ADP", "DET", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "SPACE", "VERB", "DET", "ADJ", "PROPN", "PROPN", "CCONJ", "ADV", "VERB", "DET", "NOUN", "ADV", "PUNCT", "SPACE", "ADJ", "ADP", "NOUN", "CCONJ", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "DET", "SPACE", "PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "DET", "ADJ", "ADJ", "NOUN", "NOUN", "ADP", "DET", "ADJ", "PUNCT", "ADJ", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "NOUN", "VERB", "PUNCT", "SPACE", "NOUN", "SPACE", "NUM", "SYM", "NUM", "SYM", "NUM", "SYM", "NUM"], "dep_head": [4, 3, 3, 4, 5, 5, 8, 8, 5, 8, 12, 12, 15, 15, 15, 9, 15, 18, 16, 20, 15, 23, 23, 24, 20, 24, 27, 25, 5, 28, 30, 34, 34, 34, 30, 30, 37, 30, 39, 37, 37, 30, 41, 53, 43, 44, 45, 45, 53, 52, 49, 52, 53, 68, 58, 58, 57, 58, 53, 53, 64, 64, 64, 64, 59, 68, 67, 68, 68, 68, 69, 71, 71, 75, 75, 77, 77, 78, 79, 79], "dep_rel": ["poss", "nmod", "punct", "compound", "nsubj", "ROOT", "det", "amod", "dobj", "prep", "npadvmod", "punct", "amod", "punct", "amod", "pobj", "prep", "amod", "pobj", "nsubj", "relcl", "predet", "det", "npadvmod", "advmod", "prep", "det", "pobj", "punct", "", "ROOT", "det", "amod", "compound", "dobj", "cc", "advmod", "conj", "poss", "dobj", "advmod", "punct", "", "advcl", "prep", "pobj", "cc", "conj", "punct", "poss", "", "compound", "nsubj", "ccomp", "det", "amod", "amod", "compound", "dobj", "prep", "det", "amod", "punct", "amod", "pobj", "punct", "compound", "nsubj", "ROOT", "punct", "", "ROOT", "", "quantmod", "punct", "nummod", "punct", "subtok", "punct", "ROOT"]}
{"id": "B000BUKKQ8", "docid": "B000BUKKQ8", "token": ["mfr", ":", "FRIGIDAIRE", "/", "EHP", "5.8", "CU.FT", "CAPACITY", "DRYER", "5.8", "cu", "ft", "super", "capacity", "drum", ".", "7", "auto", "dry", "cycles", ",", "4", "dryness", "level", "selections", ".", "90", "minute", "timed", "dry", ".", "Auto", "shrink", "guard", "option", ".", "Control", "lock", ".", "Cycle", "status", "lock", ".", "Drying", "rack", ".", "Electronic", "controls", ".", "Estimated", "time", "remaining", "display", ".", "Precision", "dry", "moisture", "sensor", ".", "Tumble", "care", "drying", "system", ".", "Auto", "press", "saver", "option", ".", "5", "temperature", "options", ":", "High", "heat", ",", "medium", "heat", ",", "medium", "low", "heat", ",", "low", "heat", "and", "no", "heat", ".", "On", "/", "Off", "end", "-", "of", "-", "cycle", "signal", ".", "Interior", "drum", "light", ".", "Reversible", "door", ".", "Clean", "lint", "filter", "indicator", ".", "Quick", "clean", "lint", "screen", ".", "Installation", "options&quot", ";", "Freestanding", ".", "Hidden", "(", "in", "closet", ")", ".", "Pedestal", ",", "stacked", ".", "Under", "counter", ".", "Dimensions", "27W", "x", "36&quot", ";", "H", "x", "25", "-", "1/2&apos", ";", "D.", "COLOR", "White", "  ", "Package", "Shipping", "Size", "28.00", "x", "27.00", "x", "36.00", "(", "not", "product", "dimensions", ")"], "ner": ["O", "O", "B-BRAND", "O", "O", "B-CARDINAL", "O", "O", "O", "B-QUANTITY", "I-QUANTITY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-CARDINAL", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-CARDINAL", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TIME", "I-TIME", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-CARDINAL", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-CARDINAL", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-DATE", "I-DATE", "I-DATE", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-CARDINAL", "O", "B-CARDINAL", "O", "B-CARDINAL", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "pos": ["NOUN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "SYM", "PROPN", "NUM", "PROPN", "NOUN", "PROPN", "NUM", "NOUN", "X", "ADJ", "NOUN", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "NUM", "NOUN", "ADJ", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "NUM", "NOUN", "NOUN", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "NUM", "NOUN", "VERB", "ADJ", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "NOUN", "NOUN", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "NOUN", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "VERB", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "ADJ", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "VERB", "NOUN", "VERB", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "ADJ", "NOUN", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "ADJ", "NOUN", "VERB", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "NOUN", "NOUN", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "NUM", "NOUN", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "ADJ", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "ADJ", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "ADJ", "ADJ", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "ADJ", "NOUN", "CCONJ", "DET", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "ADP", "SYM", "ADJ", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "ADP", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "ADJ", "NOUN", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "ADJ", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "ADJ", "NOUN", "NOUN", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "ADJ", "ADJ", "NOUN", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "NUM", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "VERB", "PUNCT", "ADP", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "VERB", "PUNCT", "ADP", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "NUM", "SYM", "NUM", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "SYM", "NUM", "SYM", "NUM", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "SPACE", "NOUN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "NUM", "SYM", "NUM", "SYM", "NUM", "PUNCT", "ADV", "NOUN", "NOUN", "PUNCT"], "dep_head": [0, 0, 4, 4, 7, 4, 7, 8, 0, 11, 11, 14, 13, 14, 8, 0, 19, 18, 19, 19, 19, 24, 23, 24, 19, 19, 27, 28, 29, 29, 29, 33, 33, 34, 34, 34, 37, 37, 37, 40, 41, 41, 41, 44, 44, 44, 47, 47, 47, 50, 51, 52, 52, 52, 57, 56, 57, 57, 57, 62, 62, 62, 62, 62, 66, 66, 67, 67, 67, 71, 71, 71, 71, 74, 71, 74, 77, 74, 77, 81, 81, 77, 81, 84, 81, 84, 87, 84, 71, 89, 91, 97, 97, 92, 92, 94, 94, 89, 97, 101, 101, 101, 101, 104, 104, 104, 108, 108, 109, 109, 109, 114, 114, 114, 114, 114, 116, 116, 116, 116, 116, 121, 121, 121, 123, 121, 121, 127, 129, 127, 129, 131, 131, 131, 134, 134, 137, 137, 137, 143, 143, 143, 143, 138, 147, 147, 147, 138, 147, 151, 151, 147, 151, 154, 156, 156, 156, 160, 160, 160, 156, 160], "dep_rel": ["ROOT", "punct", "nmod", "punct", "nmod", "nummod", "compound", "compound", "appos", "nummod", "nmod", "nmod", "amod", "compound", "appos", "punct", "nummod", "npadvmod", "amod", "ROOT", "punct", "nummod", "compound", "compound", "appos", "punct", "nummod", "npadvmod", "amod", "ROOT", "punct", "compound", "compound", "compound", "ROOT", "punct", "compound", "ROOT", "punct", "compound", "compound", "ROOT", "punct", "compound", "ROOT", "punct", "amod", "ROOT", "punct", "amod", "nsubj", "amod", "ROOT", "punct", "nmod", "amod", "compound", "ROOT", "punct", "compound", "compound", "compound", "ROOT", "punct", "compound", "compound", "compound", "ROOT", "punct", "nummod", "compound", "ROOT", "punct", "amod", "appos", "punct", "amod", "conj", "punct", "amod", "amod", "conj", "punct", "amod", "conj", "cc", "det", "conj", "punct", "ROOT", "punct", "nmod", "nmod", "punct", "prep", "punct", "pobj", "pobj", "punct", "compound", "compound", "ROOT", "punct", "amod", "ROOT", "punct", "amod", "compound", "compound", "ROOT", "punct", "amod", "amod", "compound", "ROOT", "punct", "ROOT", "nummod", "punct", "appos", "punct", "ROOT", "punct", "prep", "pobj", "punct", "punct", "ROOT", "punct", "acl", "punct", "ROOT", "pobj", "punct", "ROOT", "nummod", "punct", "ROOT", "punct", "nmod", "punct", "nummod", "punct", "pobj", "punct", "compound", "compound", "pobj", "", "compound", "compound", "appos", "nummod", "punct", "nummod", "punct", "ROOT", "punct", "neg", "compound", "appos", "punct"]}
{"id": "B000FTLT8I", "docid": "B000FTLT8I", "token": ["This", "item", "is", "an", "&", "ldquo;Open", "Box&rdquo", ";", "out", "of", "production", "EdgeStar", "combination", "washer", "/", "dryer", "unit.&nbsp", ";", "It", "has", "been", "fully", "tested", "by", "EdgeStar", "and", "is", "in", "perfect", "working", "order.&nbsp", ";", "The", "unit", "is", "in", "excellent", "condition", "with", "nothing", "more", "than", "possible", "minor", "cosmetic", "scratches", ".", "&", "nbsp;**Important", "note", ":", "This", "specially", "priced", "unit", "is", "not", "eligible", "for", "a", "&", "ldquo;buyer&rsquo;s", "remorse&rdquo", ";", "return", "and", "offers", "a", "30", "day", "warranty", ".", "The", "EdgeStar", "(", "CW2200", "OB", ")", "electronic", "control", "ventless", "combination", "washer", "dryer", "offers", "the", "most", "features", "for", "your", "money", "and", "the", "fastest", "dry", "time", "available", "from", "a", "ventless", "washer", "dryer", "combination", ".", "Plus", ",", "it", "is", "the", "only", "washer", "dryer", "combination", "available", "that", "runs", "off", "220V", "electricity", ".", "Among", "many", "winning", "features", ",", "this", "EdgeStar", "washer", "dryer", "combo", "features", "fully", "digital", "controls", ",", "a", "12.1", "pound", "capacity", ",", "an", "internal", "water", "heater", ",", "a", "delay", "start", "option", ",", "and", "much", ",", "much", "more", "!"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PRODUCT", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ENERGY_EFFICIENCY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ENERGY_EFFICIENCY", "B-DATE", "I-DATE", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ENERGY_EFFICIENCY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-CARDINAL", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ENERGY_EFFICIENCY", "B-QUANTITY", "I-QUANTITY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ENERGY_EFFICIENCY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "pos": ["DET", "NOUN", "VERB", "DET", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "ADP", "PUNCT", "ADP", "ADP", "NOUN", "PROPN", "NOUN", "NOUN", "SYM", "NOUN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PRON", "VERB", "VERB", "ADV", "VERB", "ADP", "PROPN", "CCONJ", "VERB", "ADP", "ADJ", "NOUN", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "DET", "NOUN", "VERB", "ADP", "ADJ", "NOUN", "ADP", "NOUN", "ADJ", "ADP", "ADJ", "ADJ", "NOUN", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "CCONJ", "ADJ", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "DET", "ADV", "VERB", "NOUN", "VERB", "ADV", "ADJ", "ADP", "DET", "CCONJ", "NUM", "NUM", "PUNCT", "VERB", "CCONJ", "VERB", "DET", "NUM", "NOUN", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "DET", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "ADJ", "NOUN", "NOUN", "NOUN", "NOUN", "NOUN", "VERB", "DET", "ADJ", "NOUN", "ADP", "DET", "NOUN", "CCONJ", "DET", "ADJ", "ADJ", "NOUN", "ADJ", "ADP", "DET", "NOUN", "NOUN", "NOUN", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "CCONJ", "PUNCT", "PRON", "VERB", "DET", "ADJ", "NOUN", "NOUN", "NOUN", "ADJ", "DET", "VERB", "ADV", "NUM", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "ADP", "ADJ", "NOUN", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "DET", "PROPN", "NOUN", "NOUN", "NOUN", "VERB", "ADV", "ADJ", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "DET", "NUM", "NOUN", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "DET", "ADJ", "NOUN", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "DET", "NOUN", "NOUN", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "CCONJ", "ADV", "PUNCT", "ADV", "ADJ", "PUNCT"], "dep_head": [1, 2, 22, 6, 6, 6, 2, 22, 22, 8, 11, 16, 16, 15, 15, 16, 9, 22, 22, 22, 22, 22, 34, 22, 23, 22, 22, 26, 30, 30, 27, 34, 33, 34, 34, 34, 37, 35, 34, 38, 39, 40, 45, 45, 45, 41, 34, 49, 49, 55, 55, 54, 53, 54, 55, 55, 55, 55, 57, 62, 61, 59, 58, 55, 55, 64, 64, 70, 69, 70, 66, 55, 73, 83, 76, 76, 83, 83, 79, 83, 81, 83, 83, 84, 84, 87, 87, 84, 87, 90, 88, 90, 95, 94, 95, 90, 95, 96, 102, 102, 101, 102, 97, 84, 107, 107, 107, 107, 112, 112, 111, 112, 107, 112, 115, 112, 115, 118, 116, 107, 130, 123, 123, 120, 130, 129, 127, 129, 129, 130, 130, 132, 133, 130, 133, 138, 137, 138, 133, 138, 143, 143, 143, 138, 143, 146, 147, 148, 130, 130, 130, 154, 154, 154, 130, 154], "dep_rel": ["det", "nsubj", "ccomp", "det", "nmod", "compound", "attr", "punct", "prep", "prep", "compound", "compound", "compound", "nmod", "punct", "compound", "pobj", "punct", "nsubjpass", "aux", "auxpass", "advmod", "ccomp", "agent", "pobj", "cc", "conj", "prep", "amod", "amod", "pobj", "punct", "det", "nsubj", "ROOT", "prep", "amod", "pobj", "prep", "pobj", "amod", "prep", "amod", "amod", "compound", "pobj", "punct", "cc", "amod", "dep", "punct", "det", "advmod", "amod", "nsubj", "ROOT", "neg", "acomp", "prep", "det", "cc", "conj", "pobj", "punct", "conj", "cc", "conj", "det", "nummod", "compound", "dobj", "punct", "det", "nmod", "punct", "nmod", "nmod", "punct", "amod", "compound", "compound", "compound", "compound", "nsubj", "ROOT", "det", "amod", "dobj", "prep", "poss", "pobj", "cc", "det", "advmod", "amod", "conj", "amod", "prep", "det", "compound", "compound", "compound", "pobj", "punct", "cc", "punct", "nsubj", "ROOT", "det", "amod", "compound", "compound", "attr", "amod", "nsubj", "relcl", "prep", "nummod", "pobj", "punct", "prep", "amod", "compound", "pobj", "punct", "det", "compound", "compound", "compound", "nsubj", "ROOT", "advmod", "amod", "dobj", "punct", "det", "nummod", "compound", "conj", "punct", "det", "amod", "compound", "conj", "punct", "det", "compound", "compound", "dobj", "punct", "cc", "amod", "punct", "advmod", "conj", "punct"]}
{"id": "B000GZ6ICS", "docid": "B000GZ6ICS", "token": ["24", "'", "'", "Compact", "Electric", "Dryer", "with", "16", "Cycles", "(", "Matches", "MAH2400", ")", "-", "MDE2400AYW"], "ner": ["B-CARDINAL", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-CARDINAL", "O", "O", "O", "B-CARDINAL", "O", "O", "O"], "pos": ["NUM", "PUNCT", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "ADP", "NUM", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PUNCT", "PROPN"], "dep_head": [5, 0, 5, 5, 5, 5, 5, 8, 6, 11, 11, 12, 13, 14, 14], "dep_rel": ["nummod", "punct", "punct", "compound", "compound", "ROOT", "prep", "nummod", "pobj", "punct", "compound", "subtok", "subtok", "punct", "ROOT"]}
{"id": "B000GZ6KIU", "docid": "B000GZ6KIU", "token": ["Features", ":", "4.0", "cu", ".", "ft", ".", "capacity", "allows", "you", "to", "do", "fewer", "loads", ",", "maximizing", "efficiency", "9", "wash", "cycles", "and", "5", "wash", "/", "rinse", "temperature", "options", "accommodate", "a", "wide", "variety", "of", "washing", "needs", "SteamFresh", "function", "uses", "steam", "to", "remove", "wrinkles", "and", "odors", ",", "reducing", "ironing", "time", "and", "trips", "to", "the", "dry", "cleaner", "19-hour", "delay", "-", "wash", "allows", "you", "to", "start", "the", "wash", "cycle", "when", "you", "'re", "not", "home", "Water", "level", "automatically", "adjusts", "to", "size", "of", "load", "for", "increased", "energy", "conservation", "Speed", "wash", "function", "saves", "time", "and", "energy", "Stainless", "-", "steel", "tub", "basket", "for", "durability", "against", "everyday", "wear", "and", "tear", "Transparent", "glass", "door", "for", "easy", "viewing", "of", "washing", "cycle", "Big", "electronic", "LCD", "display", "for", "clear", "and", "easy", "menu", "navigation", "Delayed", "start", ",", "permanent", "press", "cycle", ",", "delicate", "cycle", ",", "hand", "-", "wash", "cycle", ",", "second", "rinse", ",", "bleach", "dispenser", ",", "fabric", "dispenser", ",", "and", "pre", "-", "wash", "dispenser", ".", "Details", ":", "1", "year", "Warranty", "Parts", "and", "Labor", "Height", ":", "38", "-", "11/16", "\"", "Width", ":", "27", "\"", "Depth", ":", "29", "-", "3/4", "\"", "Capacity", ":", "4", "cubic", "feet"], "ner": ["O", "O", "B-QUANTITY", "I-QUANTITY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-CARDINAL", "O", "O", "O", "B-CARDINAL", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ENERGY_EFFICIENCY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORDINAL", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-DATE", "I-DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "B-CARDINAL", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-CARDINAL", "O", "O", "O", "B-CARDINAL", "I-CARDINAL", "I-CARDINAL", "O", "O", "O", "B-QUANTITY", "I-QUANTITY", "I-QUANTITY"], "pos": ["NOUN", "PUNCT", "NUM", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "VERB", "PRON", "PART", "VERB", "ADJ", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "VERB", "NOUN", "NUM", "NOUN", "NOUN", "CCONJ", "NUM", "NOUN", "SYM", "VERB", "NOUN", "NOUN", "VERB", "DET", "ADJ", "NOUN", "ADP", "NOUN", "VERB", "PROPN", "NOUN", "VERB", "NOUN", "PART", "VERB", "NOUN", "CCONJ", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "VERB", "NOUN", "NOUN", "CCONJ", "NOUN", "ADP", "DET", "ADJ", "ADJ", "NUM", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "VERB", "PRON", "PART", "VERB", "DET", "NOUN", "NOUN", "ADV", "PRON", "VERB", "ADV", "ADV", "PROPN", "NOUN", "ADV", "VERB", "ADP", "NOUN", "ADP", "NOUN", "ADP", "VERB", "NOUN", "NOUN", "PROPN", "NOUN", "NOUN", "VERB", "NOUN", "CCONJ", "NOUN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "NOUN", "NOUN", "ADP", "NOUN", "ADP", "ADJ", "NOUN", "CCONJ", "VERB", "ADJ", "NOUN", "NOUN", "ADP", "ADJ", "NOUN", "ADP", "NOUN", "NOUN", "ADJ", "ADJ", "NOUN", "NOUN", "ADP", "ADJ", "CCONJ", "ADJ", "NOUN", "NOUN", "VERB", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "ADJ", "NOUN", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "ADJ", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "ADJ", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "CCONJ", "ADJ", "ADJ", "ADJ", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "NUM", "NOUN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "NUM", "SYM", "NUM", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "NUM", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "NUM", "SYM", "NUM", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "NUM", "ADJ", "NOUN"], "dep_head": [0, 0, 3, 3, 3, 5, 5, 8, 8, 11, 11, 8, 13, 11, 11, 11, 19, 19, 19, 15, 19, 26, 24, 24, 25, 26, 19, 11, 30, 30, 27, 30, 31, 11, 35, 36, 36, 36, 39, 36, 39, 40, 40, 39, 39, 46, 44, 44, 44, 48, 56, 56, 56, 56, 56, 56, 49, 36, 60, 60, 57, 63, 63, 60, 66, 66, 60, 66, 70, 70, 66, 72, 36, 72, 73, 74, 75, 76, 83, 80, 83, 82, 83, 77, 36, 84, 84, 84, 90, 90, 92, 92, 87, 92, 93, 87, 97, 95, 97, 97, 102, 102, 99, 87, 105, 103, 105, 108, 112, 111, 111, 112, 84, 112, 118, 114, 114, 118, 113, 120, 120, 120, 124, 124, 120, 124, 127, 124, 127, 131, 131, 132, 127, 132, 135, 132, 135, 138, 135, 138, 141, 138, 141, 141, 145, 146, 147, 141, 120, 149, 149, 152, 149, 154, 157, 154, 154, 157, 157, 161, 161, 163, 163, 173, 163, 163, 167, 173, 167, 171, 171, 167, 173, 157, 173, 177, 177, 173], "dep_rel": ["ROOT", "punct", "nummod", "ROOT", "punct", "ROOT", "punct", "nsubj", "ROOT", "nsubj", "aux", "ccomp", "amod", "dobj", "punct", "advcl", "nmod", "nummod", "compound", "dobj", "cc", "nummod", "nmod", "punct", "compound", "compound", "conj", "advcl", "det", "amod", "dobj", "prep", "pobj", "conj", "compound", "nsubj", "ROOT", "dobj", "aux", "xcomp", "dobj", "cc", "conj", "punct", "advcl", "compound", "dobj", "cc", "conj", "prep", "det", "amod", "amod", "punct", "compound", "punct", "pobj", "conj", "nsubj", "aux", "ccomp", "det", "compound", "dobj", "advmod", "nsubj", "advcl", "neg", "compound", "compound", "attr", "advmod", "conj", "prep", "pobj", "prep", "pobj", "prep", "amod", "compound", "compound", "compound", "compound", "pobj", "conj", "dobj", "cc", "conj", "compound", "punct", "compound", "compound", "dobj", "prep", "pobj", "prep", "amod", "pobj", "cc", "conj", "amod", "compound", "dobj", "prep", "amod", "pobj", "prep", "compound", "compound", "amod", "amod", "compound", "conj", "prep", "amod", "cc", "conj", "compound", "pobj", "amod", "ROOT", "punct", "amod", "compound", "appos", "punct", "amod", "conj", "punct", "compound", "punct", "compound", "conj", "punct", "amod", "conj", "punct", "compound", "conj", "punct", "compound", "conj", "punct", "cc", "subtok", "subtok", "amod", "conj", "punct", "ROOT", "punct", "nummod", "npadvmod", "compound", "nmod", "cc", "conj", "ROOT", "punct", "nummod", "punct", "nummod", "punct", "nmod", "punct", "appos", "punct", "nmod", "punct", "nummod", "punct", "appos", "punct", "appos", "punct", "nummod", "amod", "appos"]}
{"id": "B000GZ6KI0", "docid": "B000GZ6KI0", "token": ["White", "with", "Grey", "Accents", "NEW", "6.5", "cu", ".", "ft", ".", "Duet", "Sport(TM", ")", "High", "Efficiency", "Gas", "Dryer"], "ner": ["O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "B-QUANTITY", "I-QUANTITY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "pos": ["PROPN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "NUM", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN"], "dep_head": [4, 0, 3, 1, 4, 6, 7, 4, 8, 8, 11, 11, 11, 14, 16, 16, 16], "dep_rel": ["nsubj", "prep", "compound", "pobj", "ROOT", "nummod", "subtok", "punct", "ROOT", "punct", "nmod", "ROOT", "punct", "compound", "compound", "compound", "ROOT"]}
{"id": "B000HE8EU2", "docid": "B000HE8EU2", "token": ["Washing", "machine", "valve", ".", "The", "adapters", "can", "be", "installed", "in", "any", "position", ",", "whichever", "is", "most", "convenient", "to", "receive", "the", "tubing", ".", "Either", "connection", "may", "be", "used", "for", "the", "hot", "or", "cold", "water", "supply", ".", "Threaded", "for", "5/8", "\"", "compression", "."], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-CARDINAL", "O", "O", "O"], "pos": ["VERB", "NOUN", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "DET", "NOUN", "VERB", "VERB", "VERB", "ADP", "DET", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "DET", "VERB", "ADV", "ADJ", "PART", "VERB", "DET", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "DET", "NOUN", "VERB", "VERB", "VERB", "ADP", "DET", "ADJ", "CCONJ", "ADJ", "NOUN", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "VERB", "ADP", "NUM", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "PUNCT"], "dep_head": [0, 2, 0, 0, 5, 8, 8, 8, 8, 8, 11, 9, 8, 14, 8, 16, 14, 18, 14, 20, 18, 8, 26, 26, 26, 26, 26, 26, 33, 33, 29, 29, 33, 27, 26, 35, 35, 39, 37, 36, 35], "dep_rel": ["ROOT", "compound", "dobj", "punct", "det", "nsubjpass", "aux", "auxpass", "ROOT", "prep", "det", "pobj", "punct", "nsubj", "advcl", "advmod", "acomp", "aux", "xcomp", "det", "dobj", "punct", "preconj", "nsubjpass", "aux", "auxpass", "ROOT", "prep", "det", "amod", "cc", "conj", "compound", "pobj", "punct", "ROOT", "prep", "nummod", "punct", "pobj", "punct"]}
{"id": "B000HEA9ZA", "docid": "B000HEA9ZA", "token": ["Front", "load", "washers", "are", "highly", "energy", "and", "water", "efficient", ".", "They", "require", "approximately", "3/4", "less", "water", "than", "Top", "Loaders", ".", "All", "of", "our", "washing", "machines", "have", "the", "Energy", "Star", "rating", "."], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-CARDINAL", "I-CARDINAL", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O"], "pos": ["ADJ", "NOUN", "NOUN", "VERB", "ADV", "NOUN", "CCONJ", "NOUN", "ADJ", "PUNCT", "PRON", "VERB", "ADV", "NUM", "ADJ", "NOUN", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "DET", "ADP", "DET", "NOUN", "NOUN", "VERB", "DET", "PROPN", "PROPN", "NOUN", "PUNCT"], "dep_head": [2, 2, 3, 3, 5, 3, 5, 8, 5, 3, 11, 11, 13, 15, 15, 11, 15, 18, 16, 11, 25, 20, 24, 24, 21, 25, 29, 28, 29, 25, 25], "dep_rel": ["compound", "compound", "nsubj", "ROOT", "advmod", "attr", "cc", "npadvmod", "conj", "punct", "nsubj", "ROOT", "advmod", "nummod", "amod", "dobj", "prep", "compound", "pobj", "punct", "nsubj", "prep", "poss", "compound", "pobj", "ROOT", "det", "compound", "compound", "dobj", "punct"]}
{"id": "B000HEDV5A", "docid": "B000HEDV5A", "token": ["Black", "Cabrio", "4.5", " ", "cu", ".", "ft", ".", "Washer"], "ner": ["B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "B-QUANTITY", "I-QUANTITY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "pos": ["ADJ", "PROPN", "NUM", "SPACE", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "NOUN"], "dep_head": [1, 1, 1, 2, 4, 4, 6, 6, 8], "dep_rel": ["compound", "ROOT", "nummod", "", "ROOT", "punct", "ROOT", "punct", "ROOT"]}
{"id": "B000J6DJ8A", "docid": "B000J6DJ8A", "token": ["This", "4.9", "lbs", "Pulsater", "Washer", ",", "HLP20E", ",", "is", "perfect", "for", "small", "apartments", "or", "RV", "'s", ".", "Comes", "with", "an", "easy", "quick", "connect", "Sink", "Adaptor", "that", "can", "be", "hook", "-", "up", "when", "you", "need", "it", "or", "put", "away", "when", "you", "do", "n't", "."], "ner": ["O", "B-QUANTITY", "I-QUANTITY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "pos": ["DET", "NUM", "ADP", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "VERB", "ADJ", "ADP", "ADJ", "NOUN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PART", "PUNCT", "VERB", "ADP", "DET", "ADJ", "ADJ", "VERB", "NOUN", "NOUN", "DET", "VERB", "VERB", "VERB", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "ADV", "PRON", "VERB", "PRON", "CCONJ", "VERB", "ADV", "ADV", "PRON", "VERB", "ADV", "PUNCT"], "dep_head": [4, 2, 4, 4, 8, 4, 4, 8, 8, 8, 9, 12, 10, 12, 12, 14, 8, 17, 17, 24, 22, 22, 24, 24, 18, 27, 27, 24, 30, 30, 27, 33, 33, 27, 33, 33, 33, 36, 40, 40, 36, 40, 17], "dep_rel": ["det", "compound", "compound", "compound", "nsubj", "punct", "appos", "punct", "ROOT", "acomp", "prep", "amod", "pobj", "cc", "conj", "case", "punct", "ROOT", "prep", "det", "amod", "amod", "amod", "compound", "pobj", "nsubj", "aux", "relcl", "compound", "punct", "attr", "advmod", "nsubj", "advcl", "dobj", "cc", "conj", "advmod", "advmod", "nsubj", "advcl", "neg", "punct"]}
{"id": "B000JLIZD4", "docid": "B000JLIZD4", "token": ["LG", "dryers", "have", "smart", "features", "and", "functions", "for", "the", "most", "intelligent", "fabric", "care", ".", "Sensor", "Dry", "and", "Wrinkle", "Care", "help", "extend", "the", "life", "of", "your", "clothes", "."], "ner": ["B-BRAND", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "pos": ["PROPN", "NOUN", "VERB", "ADJ", "NOUN", "CCONJ", "NOUN", "ADP", "DET", "ADV", "ADJ", "NOUN", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PROPN", "NOUN", "VERB", "DET", "NOUN", "ADP", "DET", "NOUN", "PUNCT"], "dep_head": [1, 2, 2, 4, 2, 4, 4, 2, 12, 10, 12, 12, 7, 2, 15, 19, 15, 18, 15, 19, 19, 22, 20, 22, 25, 23, 19], "dep_rel": ["compound", "nsubj", "ROOT", "amod", "dobj", "cc", "conj", "prep", "det", "advmod", "amod", "compound", "pobj", "punct", "nmod", "nsubj", "cc", "compound", "conj", "ROOT", "xcomp", "det", "dobj", "prep", "poss", "pobj", "punct"]}
{"id": "B000JLIZES", "docid": "B000JLIZES", "token": ["The", "LG", "SteamDryer", "uses", "unparalleled", "steam", "technology", "to", "eliminate", "odors", "and", "wrinkles", ",", "while", "saving", "energy", "with", "every", "load", ".", "Brilliant", ".", "(", "Capacity", ":", "7", ".", "3", "cu", ".", "Ft", ".", ")", "The", "Sensor", "Dry", "System", "measures", "moisture", "in", "the", "drum", "during", "the", "cycle", ",", "then", "automatically", "adjusts", "the", "drying", "time", "and", "temperature", "for", "optimal", "fabric", "care", ".", "Refresh", "and", "reduce", "wrinkles", "in", "up", "to", "five", "garments", "at", "a", "time", "with", "one", "20-minute", "dryer", "cycle", ".", "The", "TrueSteam", "Technology", "generates", "real", "steam", "to", "reduce", "wrinkles", "and", "odors", ",", "and", "practically", "eliminate", "the", "need", "for", "ironing", ".", "Use", "the", "SteamSanitary", "Cycle", "to", "sanitize", "non", "-", "washable", "items", ",", "such", "as", "decorative", "pillows", ".", "EasyIron", "evenly", "and", "lightly", "moistens", "the", "load", "prior", "to", "dryer", "cycle", "end", ",", "to", "make", "ironing", "easier", "and", "more", "efficient", ".", "White", "Finish"], "ner": ["O", "B-BRAND", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-CARDINAL", "O", "B-QUANTITY", "I-QUANTITY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-CARDINAL", "I-CARDINAL", "I-CARDINAL", "O", "O", "B-ENERGY_EFFICIENCY", "O", "O", "B-CARDINAL", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "pos": ["DET", "PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "ADJ", "NOUN", "NOUN", "PART", "VERB", "NOUN", "CCONJ", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "ADP", "VERB", "NOUN", "ADP", "DET", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "ADJ", "PUNCT", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "NUM", "NOUN", "NUM", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PUNCT", "DET", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "NOUN", "ADP", "DET", "NOUN", "ADP", "DET", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "ADV", "ADV", "VERB", "DET", "VERB", "NOUN", "CCONJ", "NOUN", "ADP", "ADJ", "NOUN", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "VERB", "CCONJ", "VERB", "NOUN", "ADP", "ADP", "PART", "NUM", "NOUN", "ADP", "DET", "NOUN", "ADP", "NUM", "ADJ", "NOUN", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "DET", "PROPN", "PROPN", "VERB", "ADJ", "NOUN", "PART", "VERB", "NOUN", "CCONJ", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "CCONJ", "ADV", "VERB", "DET", "NOUN", "ADP", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "VERB", "DET", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PART", "VERB", "ADJ", "ADJ", "ADJ", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "ADJ", "ADP", "ADJ", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "ADV", "CCONJ", "ADV", "VERB", "DET", "NOUN", "ADV", "ADP", "NOUN", "NOUN", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "PART", "VERB", "NOUN", "ADJ", "CCONJ", "ADV", "ADJ", "PUNCT", "ADJ", "PROPN"], "dep_head": [2, 2, 3, 3, 6, 6, 3, 8, 3, 8, 9, 9, 3, 14, 3, 14, 14, 18, 16, 3, 20, 20, 23, 23, 23, 23, 25, 28, 28, 28, 30, 30, 30, 36, 36, 36, 37, 37, 37, 37, 41, 39, 37, 44, 42, 48, 48, 48, 48, 51, 51, 48, 51, 51, 53, 57, 57, 54, 48, 59, 59, 59, 61, 61, 66, 66, 67, 63, 61, 70, 68, 61, 75, 75, 75, 71, 59, 79, 79, 80, 80, 82, 80, 84, 80, 84, 85, 85, 80, 80, 91, 80, 93, 91, 93, 94, 80, 97, 100, 100, 97, 102, 97, 104, 105, 106, 102, 106, 109, 106, 111, 109, 97, 117, 117, 114, 114, 117, 119, 117, 117, 120, 123, 124, 121, 117, 127, 117, 129, 127, 129, 132, 129, 117, 135, 135], "dep_rel": ["det", "compound", "nsubj", "ROOT", "amod", "compound", "dobj", "aux", "xcomp", "dobj", "cc", "conj", "punct", "mark", "advcl", "dobj", "prep", "det", "pobj", "punct", "ROOT", "punct", "punct", "ROOT", "punct", "appos", "punct", "nummod", "ROOT", "punct", "ROOT", "punct", "punct", "det", "compound", "compound", "nsubj", "ROOT", "dobj", "prep", "det", "pobj", "prep", "det", "pobj", "punct", "advmod", "advmod", "ROOT", "det", "compound", "dobj", "cc", "conj", "prep", "amod", "compound", "pobj", "punct", "ROOT", "cc", "conj", "dobj", "prep", "quantmod", "quantmod", "nummod", "pobj", "prep", "det", "pobj", "prep", "nummod", "amod", "compound", "pobj", "punct", "det", "compound", "nsubj", "ROOT", "amod", "dobj", "aux", "advcl", "dobj", "cc", "conj", "punct", "cc", "advmod", "conj", "det", "dobj", "prep", "pobj", "punct", "ROOT", "det", "compound", "dobj", "aux", "xcomp", "subtok", "subtok", "amod", "dobj", "punct", "amod", "prep", "amod", "pobj", "punct", "nsubj", "advmod", "cc", "conj", "ROOT", "det", "dobj", "advmod", "prep", "compound", "compound", "pobj", "punct", "aux", "advcl", "nsubj", "ccomp", "cc", "advmod", "conj", "punct", "compound", "ROOT"]}
{"id": "B000KAYRKY", "docid": "B000KAYRKY", "token": ["White", "-", "on", "-", "White", "Whirlpool(R", ")", "Super", "Capacity", "Plus", "Electric", "Dryer"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"], "pos": ["ADJ", "PUNCT", "ADP", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN"], "dep_head": [5, 0, 0, 2, 2, 5, 5, 8, 8, 8, 11, 8], "dep_rel": ["amod", "punct", "prep", "punct", "pobj", "ROOT", "punct", "compound", "ROOT", "cc", "compound", "conj"]}
{"id": "B000L3GOIS", "docid": "B000L3GOIS", "token": ["Compatible", "with", "Frigidaire", "front", "load", "washers", "and", "dryers", "with", "a", "front", "or", "rear", "control", "consoleElevates", "your", "washer", "and", "dryer", "to", "a", "more", "convenient", "heightProvides", "a", "convenient", ",", "easily", "accessible", "storage", "drawer"], "ner": ["O", "O", "B-BRAND", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ENERGY_EFFICIENCY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-GPE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ENERGY_EFFICIENCY", "O", "O", "B-CARDINAL", "B-ENERGY_EFFICIENCY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "pos": ["ADJ", "ADP", "PROPN", "ADJ", "NOUN", "NOUN", "CCONJ", "NOUN", "ADP", "DET", "ADJ", "CCONJ", "ADJ", "NOUN", "VERB", "DET", "NOUN", "CCONJ", "NOUN", "ADP", "DET", "ADV", "ADJ", "NOUN", "DET", "ADJ", "PUNCT", "ADV", "ADJ", "NOUN", "NOUN"], "dep_head": [14, 0, 5, 5, 5, 1, 5, 5, 0, 13, 13, 10, 10, 8, 14, 16, 14, 16, 16, 14, 23, 22, 23, 19, 30, 30, 30, 28, 30, 30, 14], "dep_rel": ["acomp", "prep", "nmod", "amod", "compound", "pobj", "cc", "conj", "prep", "det", "amod", "cc", "conj", "pobj", "ROOT", "poss", "dobj", "cc", "conj", "prep", "det", "advmod", "amod", "pobj", "det", "amod", "punct", "advmod", "amod", "compound", "npadvmod"]}
{"id": "B000L3IRRO", "docid": "B000L3IRRO", "token": ["3.1", "cu", "ft", ".", "Capacity5", "Wash", "Cycles3", "Wash", "/", "Rinse", "Temperatures2", "Spin", "SpeedsExtra", "RinseVariable", "End", "Of", "Cycle", "SignalDoor", "Lock", "LightEnergy", "StarSpin", "Speeds", "(", "RPM", ")", ":", "650", "-", "900Dimensions", "(", "HWD", ")", ":", "36", "x", "26", "3/4", "x", "29", "-", "1/4", "In", "."], "ner": ["B-QUANTITY", "I-QUANTITY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "B-PRODUCT", "I-PRODUCT", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "B-CARDINAL", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "B-CARDINAL", "O", "B-CARDINAL", "I-CARDINAL", "O", "B-CARDINAL", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "pos": ["NUM", "PROPN", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "VERB", "PROPN", "PROPN", "SYM", "VERB", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "NOUN", "ADP", "NOUN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PUNCT", "NUM", "SYM", "NUM", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PUNCT", "NUM", "SYM", "NUM", "NUM", "SYM", "NUM", "SYM", "NUM", "ADP", "PUNCT"], "dep_head": [2, 2, 2, 2, 4, 5, 5, 9, 9, 10, 10, 12, 14, 14, 14, 14, 15, 21, 20, 20, 21, 21, 21, 21, 21, 21, 28, 28, 28, 30, 28, 30, 28, 36, 36, 36, 40, 36, 36, 40, 40, 41, 41], "dep_rel": ["nummod", "compound", "ROOT", "punct", "ROOT", "ROOT", "punct", "nmod", "punct", "compound", "ROOT", "compound", "compound", "compound", "ROOT", "prep", "pobj", "compound", "compound", "compound", "compound", "ROOT", "punct", "appos", "punct", "punct", "nummod", "punct", "ROOT", "punct", "appos", "punct", "punct", "nummod", "punct", "compound", "nummod", "punct", "npadvmod", "punct", "ROOT", "ROOT", "punct"]}
{"id": "B000M2P3OY", "docid": "B000M2P3OY", "token": ["&", "lt;li&gt", ";", "Capacity", "(", "Size", ")", ":", "3.2", "Cubic", "foot", "&", "lt;li&gt", ";", "Capacity", "(", "Weight", ")", ":", "18&lt;li&gt", ";", "Top", "Access", "&", "lt;li&gt", ";", "Spreckle", "Porcelain", "Tub&lt;li&gt", ";", "Knobs", "Controls&lt;li&gt", ";", "SURGILATOR", "Agitator", "Type", "&", "lt;li&gt", ";", "Cotton", "Cycle", "&", "lt;li&gt", ";", "5", "Cycles", "&", "lt;li&gt", ";", "Delicate", "Cycle", "&", "lt;li&gt", ";", "Extra", "Spin", "Cycle", "&", "lt;li&gt", ";", "Heavy", "Duty", "Cycle", "&", "lt;li&gt", ";", "Lint", "Filter", "&", "lt;li&gt", ";", "1/2", "HP", "Motor", "&", "lt;li&gt", ";", "Permanent", "Press", "Cycle", "&", "lt;li&gt", ";", "Prewash", "Cycle", "&", "lt;li&gt", ";", "Quick", "Wash", "&", "lt;li&gt", ";", "Soak", "Cycle", "&", "lt;li&gt", ";", "Standard", "Sound", "Package", "&", "lt;li&gt", ";", "3", "Temperature", "Settings", "&", "lt;li&gt", ";", "Direct", "Drive", "Wash", "System", "&", "lt;li&gt", ";", "1", "Wash", "/", "Spin", "Speeds", "&", "lt;li&gt", ";", "2", "Water", "Level", "Selections", "&", "lt;li&gt", ";", "Spreckle", "Porcelain", "Basket&lt;li&gt", ";", "Dimensions", "(", "WHD", ")", "26", "7/8", "x", "36", "x", "25", "1/2", "In", "."], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-QUANTITY", "I-QUANTITY", "I-QUANTITY", "I-QUANTITY", "I-QUANTITY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-CARDINAL", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-CARDINAL", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-CARDINAL", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-CARDINAL", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-CARDINAL", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-CARDINAL", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-WORK_OF_ART", "I-WORK_OF_ART", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-CARDINAL", "I-CARDINAL", "O", "B-CARDINAL", "O", "B-CARDINAL", "I-CARDINAL", "O", "O"], "pos": ["CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PUNCT", "NUM", "ADJ", "NOUN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "PUNCT", "NUM", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "NUM", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "NUM", "PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "ADJ", "PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "ADJ", "PROPN", "PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "NUM", "PROPN", "PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "ADJ", "PROPN", "PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "VERB", "PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "NUM", "NOUN", "PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "NUM", "PROPN", "SYM", "PROPN", "PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "NUM", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "CCONJ", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "NOUN", "PUNCT", "PROPN", "PUNCT", "NUM", "NUM", "SYM", "NUM", "SYM", "NUM", "NUM", "ADV", "PUNCT"], "dep_head": [1, 1, 1, 1, 3, 3, 3, 3, 10, 10, 3, 10, 10, 10, 10, 14, 14, 14, 3, 3, 3, 22, 3, 22, 22, 22, 27, 28, 22, 22, 31, 22, 31, 35, 35, 31, 35, 35, 35, 40, 35, 40, 40, 40, 45, 40, 45, 45, 40, 50, 40, 50, 50, 40, 55, 56, 40, 56, 56, 40, 61, 62, 40, 62, 62, 40, 67, 40, 67, 67, 35, 73, 73, 35, 73, 73, 73, 79, 79, 73, 79, 79, 73, 84, 73, 84, 84, 73, 89, 73, 89, 89, 3, 94, 3, 94, 94, 94, 100, 100, 94, 100, 100, 100, 106, 106, 100, 106, 106, 94, 111, 113, 113, 94, 113, 113, 94, 121, 121, 121, 121, 121, 121, 121, 121, 128, 127, 128, 121, 128, 128, 128, 134, 134, 134, 134, 134, 136, 136, 136, 141, 146, 141, 141, 146, 146, 136, 147, 147], "dep_rel": ["cc", "ROOT", "punct", "conj", "punct", "appos", "punct", "punct", "nummod", "amod", "appos", "cc", "conj", "punct", "conj", "punct", "appos", "punct", "punct", "appos", "punct", "compound", "conj", "cc", "conj", "punct", "compound", "compound", "conj", "punct", "compound", "conj", "punct", "compound", "compound", "conj", "cc", "conj", "punct", "compound", "conj", "cc", "conj", "punct", "nummod", "conj", "cc", "conj", "punct", "compound", "conj", "cc", "conj", "punct", "compound", "compound", "conj", "cc", "conj", "punct", "compound", "compound", "conj", "cc", "conj", "punct", "compound", "conj", "cc", "conj", "punct", "nummod", "compound", "conj", "cc", "conj", "punct", "compound", "compound", "conj", "cc", "conj", "punct", "compound", "conj", "cc", "conj", "punct", "compound", "conj", "cc", "conj", "punct", "compound", "conj", "cc", "conj", "punct", "compound", "compound", "conj", "cc", "conj", "punct", "nummod", "compound", "conj", "cc", "conj", "punct", "compound", "compound", "compound", "conj", "cc", "conj", "punct", "meta", "nmod", "punct", "compound", "ROOT", "cc", "conj", "punct", "nummod", "compound", "compound", "conj", "cc", "conj", "punct", "compound", "compound", "ROOT", "punct", "conj", "punct", "appos", "punct", "compound", "nummod", "punct", "nummod", "punct", "compound", "appos", "ROOT", "punct"]}
