{"text": "This Dormont gas connector is CSA Design Certified domestically and internationally for indoor and outdoor use with natural, manufactured, mixed, liquefied petroleum, and LP-gas air mixtures Durable, naturally corrosion-resistant 304 stainless steel construction offers an exclusive no-neck design to increase flexibility Quality flared end fittings create a metal to metal seal to ensure integrity in critical applications Manufactured domestically in the USA, all Dormont gas connectors are 100 percent leak tested to ensure consistent quality you can trust.", "labels": [[5, 12, "ORG"], [30, 50, "ORG"], [171, 173, "ORG"], [230, 233, "CARDINAL"], [357, 358, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [457, 460, "GPE"], [466, 473, "ORG"], [493, 504, "PERCENT"]]}
{"text": "The revolutionary EQUATOR EZ 3612 CEE is an amazing combination home appliance that actually washes and dries clothing in one machine! Combining these functions saves you time, space, work, energy and money. Simply put in laundry, choose settings and press \"Start\". You will return to clean, dry clothes - ready to fold and put away!  Hot air used in drying is water cooled internally - condensation flushed by water pump    Wash or Dry option    3 Wash / Rinse settings    Half load option    Auto additive dispenser    Heat -  650 / 1300 Watts    Dry Time -  0-120 minutes    Standard 115V - 60Hz - 12.8 amps power requirements    Dimensions -  33H x 24W x 23-1/2D; weighs 176 pounds    1 Year Limited P&L; Warranty", "labels": [[18, 37, "PRODUCT"], [122, 125, "CARDINAL"], [258, 263, "WORK_OF_ART"], [447, 448, "CARDINAL"], [449, 461, "ORG"], [474, 478, "CARDINAL"], [494, 498, "ORG"], [529, 532, "CARDINAL"], [549, 561, "PERSON"], [561, 574, "TIME"], [587, 591, "ORG"], [633, 643, "ORG"], [653, 656, "CARDINAL"], [675, 685, "QUANTITY"], [689, 695, "DATE"], [709, 717, "CARDINAL"]]}
{"text": "Haier's Portable 8.8 lbs. Capacity Pulsator Washing System", "labels": [[0, 5, "BRAND"], [17, 24, "QUANTITY"], [26, 58, "ORG"]]}
{"text": "Haier's Portable Pulsator Washing System with SS Tub", "labels": [[0, 5, "BRAND"], [8, 40, "ORG"]]}
{"text": "Quiet, versatile and energy efficient, this front-loading washer from the Haier family of appliances has an 11-lb. capacity and a 1.5 cu. ft. stainless steel drum. Choose from 8 fabric care wash cycles and other options like water-saving rinse and spin cycle on/off. Other features include auto select wash/rinse temperature; adjustable leveling legs and retractable casters; and detergent and fabric softener dispenser. Use it built in or freestanding. Can be stacked with the Haier 11 lb. Front Loading Dryer using the Stacking Kit (each sold separately). Haier Customer Service is available 8am-5pm CST, Monday thru Friday via JMA & Associates at 1-952-469-2155 phone, 1-952-469-3655 fax or e-mail to jmacs@frontiernet.net. Imported. 34Hx24Wx22D\". Shipping weight: 172 lbs. Curbside delivery only. This is an oversized item and requires special handling. This item will ship separately from other items. An additonal flat fee will be added at checkout. Once the order leaves the distribution center, you will be contacted by the shipper to arrange a specific time for delivery. Guest should be present at the time of delivery and will be responsible for getting the item inside.", "labels": [[74, 79, "BRAND"], [128, 129, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [130, 136, "QUANTITY"], [176, 177, "CARDINAL"], [478, 483, "BRAND"], [484, 489, "QUANTITY"], [491, 510, "ORG"], [517, 533, "PRODUCT"], [558, 563, "BRAND"], [594, 601, "DATE"], [602, 605, "ORG"], [607, 613, "DATE"], [630, 646, "ORG"], [650, 664, "CARDINAL"], [672, 673, "CARDINAL"], [694, 695, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [768, 775, "QUANTITY"], [1051, 1052, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"]]}
{"text": "Haier's 1.0 cu. ft. compact Pulsator Washer provides the convenience of at-home laundry facilities for spaces where full-size machines are not an option. It is ideal for small apartments, mobile homes, and other places where space is limited. This model features a durable stainless steel tub and gives you a choice of Heavy, Normal, or Quick Wash cycles and Low, Medium, or High water levels for the perfect combination every time. The unit plugs into any standard household 120-Volt outlet and connects quickly and easily to any sink. Get the best fit with the included fill and drain hoses and Quick-Connect sink adapter. It also offers optimum portability since it can be easily rolled away for storage. All this plus quiet operation adds up to the ultimate in compact laundry solutions.Small Yet PowerfulThis easy-to-use, compact washer features a durable stainless steel tub and uses a pulsator system rather than a traditional agitator to create a powerful and effective wash action without the twisting and pulling that an agitator can cause. The absence of an agitator also frees up additional space in the wash tub to provide you with maximum wash load capacity. The pulsating action results in superb cleaning performance in a non-abrasive wash environment. It is gentler on clothes as well, making it excellent for items such as cloth diapers, baby clothes, and delicate.Digital ControlsChoose from Heavy, Normal, or Quick Wash cycles and Low, Medium, or High electronically controlled water levels on a simple touch pad to get the perfect combination for your load every time. The electronic controls include a pause button should you need to interrupt the cycle for any reason, and a clear viewing window at the top lets you check on your laundry. LED indicator lights clearly display the cycle status, and an end-of-cycle signal alerts you when clothes are clean and ready to be removed.Easy, No-Fuss InstallationThis compact washer doesn&rsquo;t just fit into small spaces; it connects quickly and easily to any sink. Get the best fit with the included fill and drain hoses and Quick Connect sink adapter. Because the unit plugs into any standard household 120-Volt outlet it can be used virtually anywhere in your living space&mdash;no need for specialized or complicated electrical connections. All this plus outstanding portability adds up to the ultimate in compact laundry solutions.", "labels": [[0, 5, "BRAND"], [8, 14, "QUANTITY"], [28, 43, "PRODUCT"], [263, 264, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [307, 308, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [319, 332, "ORG"], [337, 347, "ORG"], [476, 484, "CARDINAL"], [851, 852, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [890, 891, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [920, 921, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [953, 954, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [1236, 1237, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [1383, 1405, "ORG"], [1411, 1424, "ORG"], [1429, 1439, "ORG"], [1514, 1515, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [1622, 1623, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [1684, 1690, "BRAND"], [1696, 1697, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [1916, 1932, "PRODUCT"], [2173, 2181, "CARDINAL"]]}
{"text": "The IQ-Touch controls on this front-load dryer make choosing a cycle easy. Pick from 11 cycles that provide proper care for clothing, towels and bedding. The Gentle Tumble dry system ensures gentle, even drying.", "labels": [[61, 62, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [85, 87, "CARDINAL"]]}
{"text": "The Koblenz space saving design of the LCK-50 compact washing machine allows it to be stored almost anywhere in the home. Weighing only 25.5 pounds, it is easy to move from one place to another.  Features a rustproof polypropylene cabinet for longer life and a wide washtub opening for easy loading and unloading.  Washer controls are easy to use with a water level indicator and 15 minute automatic timer.  Includes a hose for the gravity drain feature. Machine agitates (does not spin) This great space saver can handle up to 6.6 pounds of laundry.", "labels": [[4, 11, "GPE"], [131, 147, "MONEY"], [173, 176, "CARDINAL"], [205, 206, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [259, 260, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [315, 321, "ORG"], [352, 353, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [380, 389, "TIME"], [417, 418, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [528, 538, "QUANTITY"]]}
{"text": "Avanti W797 Washer W797 Portable Washer and Dryer", "labels": [[0, 6, "ORG"], [24, 39, "ORG"]]}
{"text": "White 2.9 cu.ft Capacity Energy Star(R) qualified, 24&quot; Wide Front-Loading Washer", "labels": [[6, 9, "CARDINAL"], [60, 85, "ORG"]]}
{"text": "Our Shoe/Boot Dryer uses a mere 36W for fan-free, silent convection of warmed air that dries all the way down to the toes.  Attach the optional Glove Attachment and safely dry your gloves overnight.    Perfect for travel and vacations, our  Portable Dryer utilizes the same thermal convection technology in a compact, packable design; power adapter included.     Size  10\"W x 9-1/2\"D x 22\"H", "labels": [[25, 26, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [144, 160, "PERSON"], [188, 197, "TIME"], [241, 255, "ORG"], [307, 308, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [363, 367, "PERSON"], [369, 373, "CARDINAL"], [376, 377, "CARDINAL"]]}
{"text": "mfr: FRIGIDAIRE/EHP 5.8 CU.FT CAPACITY DRYER 5.8 cu ft super capacity drum. 7 auto dry cycles, 4 dryness level selections. 90 minute timed dry. Auto shrink guard option. Control lock. Cycle status lock. Drying rack. Electronic controls. Estimated time remaining display. Precision dry moisture sensor. Tumble care drying system. Auto press saver option. 5 temperature options: High heat, medium heat, medium low heat, low heat and no heat. On/Off end-of-cycle signal. Interior drum light. Reversible door. Clean lint filter indicator. Quick clean lint screen.Installation options&quot; Freestanding. Hidden (in closet). Pedestal, stacked. Under counter. Dimensions 27W x 36&quot; H x 25-1/2&apos; D. COLOR White   Package Shipping Size 28.00 x 27.00 x 36.00 (not product dimensions)", "labels": [[5, 15, "BRAND"], [20, 23, "CARDINAL"], [45, 51, "QUANTITY"], [76, 77, "CARDINAL"], [95, 96, "CARDINAL"], [123, 132, "TIME"], [354, 355, "CARDINAL"], [572, 584, "CARDINAL"], [620, 628, "ORG"], [684, 695, "DATE"], [697, 711, "PERSON"], [736, 741, "CARDINAL"], [744, 749, "CARDINAL"], [752, 757, "CARDINAL"]]}
{"text": "This item is an &ldquo;Open Box&rdquo; out of production EdgeStar combination washer/dryer unit.&nbsp; It has been fully tested by EdgeStar and is in perfect working order.&nbsp; The unit is in excellent condition with nothing more than possible minor cosmetic scratches. &nbsp;**Important note: This specially priced unit is not eligible for a &ldquo;buyer&rsquo;s remorse&rdquo; return and offers a 30 day warranty. The EdgeStar (CW2200 OB) electronic control ventless combination washer dryer offers the most features for your money and the fastest dry time available from a ventless washer dryer combination. Plus, it is the only washer dryer combination available that runs off 220V electricity. Among many winning features, this EdgeStar washer dryer combo features fully digital controls, a 12.1 pound capacity, an internal water heater, a delay start option, and much, much more!", "labels": [[16, 17, "PRODUCT"], [57, 65, "ORG"], [131, 139, "ORG"], [343, 344, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [399, 400, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [401, 407, "DATE"], [422, 430, "ORG"], [432, 441, "PERSON"], [576, 577, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [683, 687, "CARDINAL"], [735, 743, "ORG"], [796, 797, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [798, 808, "QUANTITY"], [845, 846, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"]]}
{"text": "24'' Compact Electric Dryer with 16 Cycles (Matches MAH2400) - MDE2400AYW", "labels": [[0, 2, "CARDINAL"], [5, 27, "ORG"], [33, 35, "CARDINAL"], [52, 59, "CARDINAL"]]}
{"text": "Features: 4.0 cu. ft. capacity allows you to do fewer loads, maximizing efficiency 9 wash cycles and 5 wash/rinse temperature options accommodate a wide variety of washing needs SteamFresh function uses steam to remove wrinkles and odors, reducing ironing time and trips to the dry cleaner 19-hour delay-wash allows you to start the wash cycle when you're not home Water level automatically adjusts to size of load for increased energy conservation Speed wash function saves time and energy Stainless-steel tub basket for durability against everyday wear and tear Transparent glass door for easy viewing of washing cycle Big electronic LCD display for clear and easy menu navigation Delayed start, permanent press cycle, delicate cycle, hand-wash cycle, second rinse, bleach dispenser, fabric dispenser, and pre-wash dispenser. Details: 1 year Warranty Parts and Labor Height: 38-11/16\" Width: 27\" Depth: 29-3/4\" Capacity: 4 cubic feet", "labels": [[10, 16, "QUANTITY"], [83, 84, "CARDINAL"], [101, 102, "CARDINAL"], [146, 147, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [178, 188, "ORG"], [491, 506, "ORG"], [754, 760, "ORDINAL"], [837, 843, "DATE"], [869, 875, "PERSON"], [877, 879, "CARDINAL"], [894, 896, "CARDINAL"], [905, 911, "CARDINAL"], [923, 935, "QUANTITY"]]}
{"text": "White with Grey Accents NEW 6.5 cu. ft. Duet Sport(TM) High Efficiency Gas Dryer", "labels": [[11, 27, "ORG"], [28, 34, "QUANTITY"]]}
{"text": "Washing machine valve. The adapters can be installed in any position, whichever is most convenient to receive the tubing. Either connection may be used for the hot or cold water supply. Threaded for 5/8\" compression.", "labels": [[199, 202, "CARDINAL"]]}
{"text": "Front load washers are highly energy and water efficient. They require approximately 3/4 less water than Top Loaders. All of our washing machines have the Energy Star rating.", "labels": [[71, 88, "CARDINAL"], [105, 116, "PERSON"], [155, 166, "ORG"]]}
{"text": "Black Cabrio 4.5  cu. ft. Washer", "labels": [[0, 12, "PERSON"], [13, 18, "QUANTITY"]]}
{"text": "&lt;li&gt; 1/2 HP Motor&lt;li&gt; Energy Star Qualified&lt;li&gt; Extra Rinse Cycle&lt;li&gt; Heavy Duty Cycle&lt;li&gt; 4 Water Temperature Options&lt;li&gt; 10 Number of Wash Cycles&lt;li&gt; Detergent, Fabric Softener, Bleach Dispensers&lt;li&gt; Quiet Wash Sound Insulation Package&lt;li&gt; Spin Speed (RPM): 1100&lt;li&gt; Dimensions: (WHD) 27 x 36 x 30 In.", "labels": [[11, 14, "CARDINAL"], [15, 17, "ORG"], [34, 45, "ORG"], [66, 77, "PRODUCT"], [94, 104, "ORG"], [121, 122, "CARDINAL"], [159, 161, "CARDINAL"], [205, 220, "ORG"], [222, 228, "PERSON"], [250, 294, "ORG"], [296, 311, "ORG"], [314, 327, "ORG"], [329, 339, "ORG"], [342, 345, "ORG"], [347, 349, "CARDINAL"], [352, 354, "CARDINAL"], [357, 359, "CARDINAL"]]}
{"text": "&lt;li&gt; AccuDry Sensing System   &lt;li&gt; AccelerCare Drying System&lt;li&gt; 9 Automatic Cycles &lt;li&gt; Delicate Cycle   &lt;li&gt; Heavy Duty Cycle &lt;li&gt; Normal Cycle &lt;li&gt; Quick Dry Cycle &lt;li&gt; End-of-Cycle Signal &lt;li&gt; Wrinkle Shield Plus Feature (90 Minutes)   &lt;li&gt; 5 Temperature Selections &lt;li&gt; Quiet Dry Noise Reduction   &lt;li&gt; Innovative Suspension System   &lt;li&gt; Dryer Door Window &lt;li&gt; Reversible Side-Swing Door &lt;li&gt; Electronic Controls &lt;li&gt; Child Lockout &lt;li&gt; Front-Mounted Lint Screen   &lt;li&gt; Interior Drum Light &lt;li&gt; 4-Way Venting   &lt;li&gt; Optional Storage Pedestals &lt;li&gt; Dimensions: (HWD) 36 x 27 x 32 7/8 In.", "labels": [[11, 45, "ORG"], [47, 58, "ORG"], [83, 84, "CARDINAL"], [85, 111, "ORG"], [113, 139, "ORG"], [141, 167, "ORG"], [169, 191, "ORG"], [199, 218, "ORG"], [251, 270, "ORG"], [280, 290, "TIME"], [305, 306, "CARDINAL"], [307, 339, "ORG"], [341, 378, "ORG"], [380, 420, "ORG"], [422, 449, "ORG"], [451, 487, "PERSON"], [489, 518, "ORG"], [520, 543, "ORG"], [545, 582, "ORG"], [584, 613, "ORG"], [615, 640, "ORG"], [642, 678, "ORG"], [693, 696, "ORG"], [698, 700, "CARDINAL"], [708, 714, "CARDINAL"]]}
{"text": "This 4.9 lbs Pulsater Washer, HLP20E, is perfect for small apartments or RV's. Comes with an easy quick connect Sink Adaptor that can be hook-up when you need it or put away when you don't.", "labels": [[5, 12, "QUANTITY"], [73, 75, "PERSON"], [112, 124, "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "LG dryers have smart features and functions for the most intelligent fabric care. Sensor Dry and Wrinkle Care help extend the life of your clothes.", "labels": [[0, 2, "BRAND"], [82, 92, "ORG"], [97, 109, "ORG"]]}
{"text": "The LG SteamDryer uses unparalleled steam technology to eliminate odors and wrinkles, while saving energy with every load. Brilliant. (Capacity: 7. 3 cu. Ft. ) The Sensor Dry System measures moisture in the drum during the cycle, then automatically adjusts the drying time and temperature for optimal fabric care. Refresh and reduce wrinkles in up to five garments at a time with one 20-minute dryer cycle. The TrueSteam Technology generates real steam to reduce wrinkles and odors, and practically eliminate the need for ironing. Use the SteamSanitary Cycle to sanitize non-washable items, such as decorative pillows. EasyIron evenly and lightly moistens the load prior to dryer cycle end, to make ironing easier and more efficient. White Finish", "labels": [[4, 6, "BRAND"], [145, 146, "CARDINAL"], [148, 152, "QUANTITY"], [160, 181, "ORG"], [345, 355, "CARDINAL"], [368, 369, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [380, 383, "CARDINAL"], [407, 431, "ORG"]]}
{"text": "White-on-White Whirlpool(R) Super Capacity Plus Electric Dryer", "labels": [[28, 62, "ORG"]]}
{"text": "Compatible with Frigidaire front load washers and dryers with a front or rear control consoleElevates your washer and dryer to a more convenient heightProvides a convenient, easily accessible storage drawer", "labels": [[16, 26, "BRAND"], [62, 63, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [86, 101, "GPE"], [127, 128, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [145, 159, "CARDINAL"], [160, 161, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"]]}
{"text": "3.1 cu ft. Capacity5 Wash Cycles3 Wash/Rinse Temperatures2 Spin SpeedsExtra RinseVariable End Of Cycle SignalDoor Lock LightEnergy StarSpin Speeds (RPM) : 650 - 900Dimensions (HWD): 36 x 26 3/4 x 29-1/4 In.", "labels": [[0, 6, "QUANTITY"], [64, 75, "ORG"], [119, 130, "ORG"], [131, 146, "PRODUCT"], [148, 151, "ORG"], [155, 158, "CARDINAL"], [176, 179, "ORG"], [182, 184, "CARDINAL"], [187, 193, "CARDINAL"], [196, 198, "CARDINAL"]]}
{"text": "5.8 cu.ft. Capacity Dryer", "labels": [[0, 3, "CARDINAL"], [4, 9, "ORG"]]}
{"text": "Frigidaire AGQ7000EG Affinity Dryer - Glacier Blue - Gas", "labels": [[0, 10, "BRAND"], [21, 56, "ORG"]]}
{"text": "&lt;li&gt; Capacity (Size): 3.2 Cubic foot &lt;li&gt; Capacity (Weight): 18&lt;li&gt; Top Access &lt;li&gt; Spreckle Porcelain Tub&lt;li&gt; Knobs Controls&lt;li&gt; SURGILATOR Agitator Type &lt;li&gt; Cotton Cycle &lt;li&gt; 5 Cycles &lt;li&gt; Delicate Cycle &lt;li&gt; Extra Spin Cycle &lt;li&gt; Heavy Duty Cycle &lt;li&gt; Lint Filter &lt;li&gt; 1/2 HP Motor &lt;li&gt; Permanent Press Cycle &lt;li&gt; Prewash Cycle &lt;li&gt; Quick Wash &lt;li&gt; Soak Cycle &lt;li&gt; Standard Sound Package &lt;li&gt; 3 Temperature Settings &lt;li&gt; Direct Drive Wash System &lt;li&gt; 1 Wash/Spin Speeds &lt;li&gt; 2 Water Level Selections &lt;li&gt; Spreckle Porcelain Basket&lt;li&gt; Dimensions (WHD) 26 7/8 x 36 x 25 1/2 In.", "labels": [[28, 52, "QUANTITY"], [73, 84, "CARDINAL"], [108, 116, "PERSON"], [141, 146, "ORG"], [166, 200, "ORG"], [202, 224, "ORG"], [226, 227, "CARDINAL"], [228, 244, "ORG"], [246, 270, "ORG"], [272, 298, "ORG"], [300, 326, "ORG"], [328, 349, "ORG"], [351, 354, "CARDINAL"], [355, 373, "ORG"], [375, 406, "ORG"], [408, 431, "ORG"], [439, 453, "ORG"], [455, 475, "ORG"], [477, 509, "ORG"], [511, 512, "CARDINAL"], [513, 543, "ORG"], [545, 579, "ORG"], [581, 582, "CARDINAL"], [583, 609, "ORG"], [611, 612, "CARDINAL"], [613, 645, "ORG"], [647, 665, "WORK_OF_ART"], [695, 698, "ORG"], [700, 706, "CARDINAL"], [709, 711, "CARDINAL"], [714, 720, "CARDINAL"]]}
{"text": "Bosch Axxis WFL2090UC Front Load White Washer, Model WFL2090 Key Features: Performance Logixx&trade; Control By selecting a fabric selection/water temperature, the Axxis&trade; and Axxis+&trade; washing machine will automatically determine every other necessary aspect in delivering excellent washing results. Water level - the proper amount of water for the fabric type. Temperature - range of temperatures allowed for a chosen fabric type. Tumble Action Time & Speed - how long the laundry is tumbled and at how many revolutions per minute. Soak Time - how long the laundry soaks in the solution of water and detergent. Drum Reversing Rhythms - how the laundry is tumbled back and forth based on fabric selection. Spin Speed - controls the maximum spin speed allowed for a given fabric setting. Rinses - number of rinses and amount of water necessary for each specific load. Detergent Efficiency System The Bosch Detergent Efficiency System in the Axxis&trade; and Axxis+&trade; Washers contains laundry detergent within the active washing area of the system: the Eco-Ball rises and seals off the sump and stays in this position until the the drain cycle. Further, it prevents heavier detergent from settling into the bottom of the sump before it is dissolved. Therefore, the recommended dose of detergent is maintained in the system for better cleaning and \"unused\" detergent is kept from entering into our water ways. ENERGY STAR Qualified Your home will benefit from appliances that feature the Energy Star logo, which symbolizes that the appliance is significantly more energy efficient than the average comparable model. Look for the Energy Star label on Bosch laundry and dishwasher products. These products beat the set energy conservation standards by saving even more money and using even less energy. The energy efficiencies of a Bosch appliance are detailed on an EnergyGuide label. If you don't see an EnergyGuide label on a Bosch appliance, please ask a...", "labels": [[0, 5, "BRAND"], [47, 60, "PRODUCT"], [101, 111, "ORG"], [122, 123, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [164, 175, "PERSON"], [181, 193, "PERSON"], [420, 421, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [442, 468, "ORG"], [543, 552, "WORK_OF_ART"], [622, 644, "PRODUCT"], [773, 774, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [909, 914, "BRAND"], [967, 979, "PERSON"], [1062, 1074, "ORG"], [1500, 1511, "ORG"], [1641, 1652, "ORG"], [1662, 1667, "BRAND"], [1840, 1841, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [1842, 1847, "BRAND"], [1877, 1888, "ORG"], [1916, 1927, "ORG"], [1937, 1938, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [1939, 1944, "BRAND"], [1967, 1968, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"]]}
{"text": "Color: White 9 lbs Capacity  Stainless Steel Tub and Drum 4 Water Level Settings 3 Temperature Settings (Hot, Warm and Cold)  5 Cycles Fabric Selection Options  Includes Caster Wheels Energy Efficient Full Length Agitator Quiet Operation", "labels": [[13, 18, "QUANTITY"], [29, 48, "ORG"], [53, 123, "WORK_OF_ART"], [126, 127, "CARDINAL"], [128, 159, "EVENT"], [213, 237, "EVENT"]]}
{"text": "Is living space at a premium? Hate the laundromat? Consider our compact lightweight clothes washer which is perfectly sized for small households. The quick connect attachment fits most standard faucets so you don't need direct plumbing.  Features rolling castors and a wash load capacity of up to 10 lbs.", "labels": [[19, 20, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [267, 268, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [291, 303, "QUANTITY"]]}
{"text": "DBXR463EGWW - GE(R) 6.0 Cu. Ft. Extra-Large Capacity Electric Dryer", "labels": [[0, 18, "ORG"], [20, 26, "QUANTITY"], [38, 67, "ORG"]]}
{"text": "Whirlpool Duet Series WED9400SZ 27'' Electric Dryer with 10 Automatic Cycles, Enhanced Sound Package, Wrinkle Protection & Interior Drum Light: White-Blue Metallic Water Drop", "labels": [[0, 9, "BRAND"], [57, 59, "CARDINAL"], [60, 76, "ORG"], [102, 131, "ORG"]]}
{"text": "3.6 cu ft Front Load Washer 1050 RPM Silver Door Trim - White", "labels": [[0, 6, "QUANTITY"], [28, 32, "CARDINAL"]]}
{"text": "The remaining time display on this dyer indicates how much time is left in the current cycle and the end of cycle beeper alerts you when time is up, so you don't have to check and see if the dryer has stopped. Intuitive controls make navigating the numerous settings and features simple.", "labels": []}
{"text": "High Efficiency front load washerHolds up to a king sized comforter12 pre-set cycles and 6 optional cyclesStainless steel drum1300 RPM max. spin speedElectronic controlsDelay Start up to 24 hrs.Blue Onyx BodyMatching Dryers: DV337AEL-electric / DV337AGL-gasDimension: (WHD) 27 x 38 x 31 In.", "labels": [[45, 46, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [89, 90, "CARDINAL"], [100, 115, "EVENT"], [131, 134, "ORG"], [187, 193, "TIME"], [194, 223, "ORG"], [269, 272, "ORG"], [274, 276, "CARDINAL"], [279, 281, "CARDINAL"], [284, 286, "CARDINAL"]]}
{"text": "Frigidaire ATF6000FS Frigidaire King Size 3.5 Cu. Feet Front Loader Washer.", "labels": [[0, 10, "BRAND"], [21, 31, "BRAND"], [42, 48, "QUANTITY"], [50, 60, "PRODUCT"], [61, 74, "PRODUCT"]]}
{"text": "White Whirlpool(R) Duet(R) Super Capacity Plus Front-Load Electric Dryer", "labels": []}
{"text": "Compact laundry solution for small spaces with no venting capabilities, making it the perfect companion for small homes, apartments, cabins, RVs, and boats. Haier's washer and dryer combo model makes it possible for you to do it all in one step! Put in a dirty load, and with the touch of a button, it'll come out fresh, dry, and smelling sweet. It's a great time-saver for busy families that need to do laundry frequently. Key features include: auto select wash and rinse temperatures; water-saving rinse option; self-locking door; adjustable leveling legs; and a 1 year warranty. The Haier Ventless Washer/Dryer Combo HWD1000 is an elegant all-in-one solution for the vexing problems of limited space and lack of venting", "labels": [[157, 162, "BRAND"], [236, 239, "CARDINAL"], [253, 254, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [289, 290, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [351, 352, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [563, 564, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [565, 580, "DATE"], [586, 591, "BRAND"], [620, 627, "PRODUCT"], [649, 652, "CARDINAL"]]}
{"text": "XL Capacity (4.0 cu.ft. IEC)Direct Drive Motor for the ultimate in durability and reliability1100 RPM maximum spin for efficient water extractionIntelligent Fabric CareSenseClean System for intelligent fabric care, water and energy efficiencyWater Heater7 Washing Programs5 Temperature Levels4 Tray Detergent DispenserRollerJetsSanitary CycleDelay Wash by 19 hours for washing convenienceUpfront Electronic Control Panel with Dial-A-CycleChrome Rimmed Door with Clear GlassStackable with Matching Dryer (DLE3733/DLG3744)Optional Drawer PedestalEnvironmentally FriendlyLoDecibel Quiet OperationHighly Energy and Water EfficientWidth : 27\"Depth : 29 3/4\"Height : 38 11/16\"", "labels": [[0, 11, "ORG"], [13, 16, "CARDINAL"], [17, 22, "ORG"], [24, 46, "ORG"], [98, 101, "ORG"], [135, 185, "ORG"], [248, 273, "PERSON"], [337, 352, "PERSON"], [356, 364, "TIME"], [377, 420, "ORG"], [431, 432, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [488, 502, "ORG"], [578, 631, "ORG"], [645, 647, "CARDINAL"], [661, 669, "CARDINAL"]]}
{"text": "The Whirlpool 5 Cycle Large Capacity Washer with Electric Dryer is the perfect solution for a small laundry space.  This washer/dryer set fits in small spaces and provides all of the great cleaning and fabric care you expect from a standard machine.  The washer features a 1.5 cu. ft. capacity, spreckle porcelain basket, 5 automatic cycles, 4 wash/rinse temperature combinations, 5 wash/spin speed combinations, 3 water level selections, easy-to-clean lint filter, and ToughTop II top and lid finish.  The dryer features 5 cycles, 4 temperature selections, side-swing door, end-of-cycle signal, and automatic Dry-Miser control.", "labels": [[4, 13, "BRAND"], [49, 63, "ORG"], [92, 93, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [230, 231, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [271, 272, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [322, 323, "CARDINAL"], [342, 343, "CARDINAL"], [381, 382, "CARDINAL"], [413, 414, "CARDINAL"], [470, 481, "ORG"], [522, 523, "CARDINAL"], [532, 533, "CARDINAL"]]}
{"text": "Ne xx t 300 Series Washer", "labels": [[0, 7, "PERSON"], [8, 11, "CARDINAL"]]}
{"text": "Package Content:DryermanualwarrantyQuick fluff, heatless settingOptional wrinkle care4 heat selections provide the right temperature for you drying needsQuiet-By-Design sound package mutes most soundsRotary electric controlsHeight 42.00Width 27.00Depth 28.25Weight 115.00Color White, Silver BackguardOperating SystemBatteries IncludedBatteries RequiredNumber of Batteries 0Battery Type no batteries requiredLanguage EnglishAssembly Required", "labels": [[16, 40, "ORG"], [194, 206, "LOC"], [216, 230, "ORG"], [253, 264, "CARDINAL"], [277, 358, "ORG"], [399, 431, "ORG"]]}
{"text": "This powerful washer's SenseClean system automatically adjusts water level and wash time according to load size and weight for enhanced performance. The sanitary cycle heats water to 158 to help remove heavy soils.", "labels": [[23, 33, "ORG"], [183, 186, "CARDINAL"]]}
{"text": "Energy Star 24'' Compact Front Load Washer with 22 Cycles - MAH2400A", "labels": [[0, 16, "ORG"], [17, 42, "ORG"], [48, 50, "CARDINAL"]]}
{"text": "GE is one of the largest manufacturers of major appliances in the world. Since 1907, they have been introducing advanced appliances to improve peoples' lives and conserve electricity. They continue that legacy today with innovations like the Advantium(R) oven, the Harmony(TM) clothes care system, and more. This super capacity dryer from GE features a stainless steel drum interior and a Sensor Dry Plus moisture sensor. It also includes Wrinkle Care, as well as Damp Dry and Dewrinkle cycles.", "labels": [[0, 2, "BRAND"], [79, 83, "DATE"], [210, 215, "DATE"], [339, 341, "BRAND"], [351, 352, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [387, 388, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [389, 404, "PRODUCT"], [439, 451, "ORG"], [464, 472, "ORG"], [477, 486, "ORG"]]}
{"text": "Type Front Loader Yes Design Look Front Control Intelligent Electronic Controls With Dual Led Display Yes Dial-a-cycle&trade; Yes Capacity 7.3 Cu.ft. (doe) Dry Linen Capacity >10.1 Kg Drying Programs 9 Programs Sensor Dry: Normal, Cotton/towels, Delicates, Wrinkle Care, Heavy Duty, Ultra Delicate Manual Dry: Speed Dry, Air Dry, Freshen Up 7 Options Custom Program, Damp Dry Beep, Wrinkle Care, Rack Dry, Anti Bacterial, Child Lock, Beep On/off 5 Temperature Levels High, Medium High, Medium, Low, Ultra Low 5 Drying Levels Very Dry, More Dry, Normal Dry, Less Dry, Damp Dry Dry Times 60 Min., 50 Min., 40 Min., 30 Min., 20 Min., More Time, Less Time Fabric Care Features Sensor Dry Yes Precise Temperature Control With Variable Heater Yes Convenience Features End Of Cycle Beeper Variable Venting Option Electric: 4 Way Venting Gas: 3 Way Venting Flowsense&trade; Duct Clogging Indicator Yes Drum Light Yes Reversible Door Yes Remaining Time Display/status Indicator(s) Yes Leveling Legs 4 Adjustable Legs Drying Rack Yes Lodecibel&trade; Quiet Operation 58 Db Materials And Finishes Neverust&trade; Stainless Steel Drum Yes Top Plate Painted Cabinet Painted Steel Control Panel Plastic Transparent Door Glass Yes Door Rim Chrome Available Colors White (w), Pearl Gray (g) Power Source Ratings Ul Listed Requirements Gas: 120v, 15 Amps Electric: 120/240v, 30 Amps Type Gas (dlg5966)/electric (dle5955) Options Pedestal Wdp3w, Wdp3g (drawer With Handle) Pedestal (wxhxd) 27\" X 13 3/5\" X 28 2/5\" Stacking Kit Wstk1, Gstk1 Dimensions Product ( Wxhxd) 27\" X 39\" X 28 1/3\" (50 1/2\"d With Door Open) Carton (wxhxd) 29 1/2\" X 43 5/16\" X 31 5/16\" Product Weight / Shipping Weight 126 Lbs / 144 Lbs Warranty Limited Warranty 90 Days From Refurbking Inc.", "labels": [[111, 112, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [139, 142, "CARDINAL"], [143, 148, "ORG"], [156, 174, "ORG"], [176, 180, "CARDINAL"], [200, 201, "CARDINAL"], [246, 255, "ORG"], [321, 328, "ORG"], [330, 365, "ORG"], [367, 380, "PERSON"], [382, 394, "PERSON"], [396, 404, "PERSON"], [446, 447, "CARDINAL"], [509, 510, "CARDINAL"], [586, 593, "PERCENT"], [598, 602, "GPE"], [636, 640, "ORG"], [642, 651, "ORG"], [816, 817, "CARDINAL"], [835, 836, "CARDINAL"], [992, 1019, "ORG"], [1041, 1059, "EVENT"], [1102, 1122, "ORG"], [1260, 1270, "PERSON"], [1272, 1273, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [1324, 1328, "PRODUCT"], [1330, 1332, "CARDINAL"], [1333, 1346, "ORG"], [1358, 1360, "CARDINAL"], [1361, 1374, "ORG"], [1432, 1433, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [1442, 1463, "ORG"], [1472, 1474, "CARDINAL"], [1478, 1484, "CARDINAL"], [1488, 1494, "CARDINAL"], [1496, 1508, "ORG"], [1550, 1552, "DATE"], [1556, 1558, "CARDINAL"], [1562, 1568, "CARDINAL"], [1571, 1579, "CARDINAL"], [1611, 1617, "CARDINAL"], [1621, 1628, "CARDINAL"], [1632, 1639, "CARDINAL"], [1641, 1673, "WORK_OF_ART"], [1674, 1683, "QUANTITY"], [1718, 1725, "DATE"], [1731, 1746, "ORG"]]}
{"text": "Biscuit Whirlpool(R) 10 in. Laundry Pedestal", "labels": [[0, 7, "PERSON"], [21, 23, "CARDINAL"]]}
{"text": "Connects to any 120-Volt outlet and matches any Haier Portable Washer. Just mount to a wall and you're set. 4 dryer cycle settings, 3 temperature settings, and drying timer.", "labels": [[16, 24, "CARDINAL"], [48, 53, "BRAND"], [85, 86, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [108, 109, "CARDINAL"], [132, 133, "CARDINAL"]]}
{"text": "Frigidaire Gallery Series: GLGQ2152E 27'' Gas Dryer with 5.8 Cu. Ft. Capacity, 7 Auto Dry Cycles & Electronic Controls", "labels": [[0, 10, "BRAND"], [57, 63, "QUANTITY"], [79, 80, "CARDINAL"], [81, 118, "ORG"]]}
{"text": "White w/ Gray Accents Whirlpool(R) Duet Sport(TM) HT Front-Loading Washer ENERGY STAR(R) Qualified", "labels": [[0, 34, "ORG"]]}
{"text": "Residential commercial washer with factory equipped coin slide adjustable to $2 (8 quarters) per cycle.", "labels": [[78, 79, "MONEY"], [81, 91, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Ne xx t 500 Series Washer", "labels": [[0, 7, "PERSON"], [8, 11, "CARDINAL"]]}
{"text": "LG DLE3733 27'' Stackable Electric Dryer with 7.3 cu. ft. Capacity, Sensor Dry System and Dial-A-Cycle", "labels": [[0, 2, "BRAND"], [3, 14, "MONEY"], [16, 40, "ORG"], [46, 52, "QUANTITY"], [68, 89, "ORG"], [95, 96, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"]]}
{"text": "Bravos Electric Dryer", "labels": [[0, 21, "ORG"]]}
{"text": "Centennial Top-Load Washer", "labels": [[0, 26, "ORG"]]}
{"text": "White with Grey Accents NEW 3.3 cu.ft. Capacity Duet Sport(TM) Fabric Care System", "labels": [[11, 27, "ORG"], [28, 31, "CARDINAL"], [32, 37, "PRODUCT"]]}
{"text": "Miele W3035 24\" Front Load Washer with 2.52 cu. ft. Capacity, 11 Wash Programs, Stainless Steel Honeycomb Drum and Angled Digital Control Panel: Stainless Steel", "labels": [[0, 5, "BRAND"], [12, 14, "CARDINAL"], [16, 33, "ORG"], [39, 46, "QUANTITY"], [62, 64, "CARDINAL"], [65, 78, "ORG"], [80, 110, "ORG"], [122, 160, "ORG"]]}
{"text": "Whirlpool Compact Electric Dryer 3.4 Cu. Ft. Capacity  AccuDry Sensing System  3 Cycles  End-of-Cycle Signal  2 Temperature Settings  Side-Swing Door  Interior Lint Screen", "labels": [[0, 9, "BRAND"], [33, 39, "QUANTITY"], [55, 77, "ORG"], [79, 80, "CARDINAL"], [81, 87, "NORP"], [110, 111, "CARDINAL"], [160, 171, "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "White Duet Whirlpool Washer", "labels": [[11, 20, "BRAND"]]}
{"text": "Together, Whirlpool and Maytag emerge a more compelling company positioned to deliver the most innovative portfolio of products and services to consumers throughout the world. Together, they will continue to find new ways to delight consumers while striving to fulfill their vision of Every Home . . . Everywhere with Pride, Passion and Performance.High performance is instantly evident in this 3.7 cu. ft. front load washer. With a King Size Capacity, this washer offers ample room to wash and care for all your loads of laundry, even king-size bedding. The brand-exclusive Rainfall Clean wash system uses a unique 3-baffle design to scoop up water and thoroughly shower it onto fabrics for optimum saturation and cleaning performance.Exclusive Rainfall Clean Wash System with Sensi-Care technology10 Automatic Wash Cycles4 Wash Options Including Exclusive MaxExtract Extended Spin5 Temperature Settings10-Hour Delay Start OptionIntelliT", "labels": [[10, 19, "BRAND"], [24, 30, "BRAND"], [38, 39, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [285, 295, "ORG"], [390, 401, "QUANTITY"], [431, 432, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [433, 451, "ORG"], [575, 589, "ORG"], [607, 608, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [778, 816, "PRODUCT"]]}
{"text": "White Whirlpool(R) Cabrio(TM) Ultra Capacity Plus Washer ENERGY STAR(R) Qualified", "labels": []}
{"text": "Stainless Steel Honeycomb&trade; Drum - Forged from the very best stainless steel with a unique convex pattern that resembles a honeycomb, the HoneycombTM drum enhances both cleaning performance and reduces fabric wear.Advanced Touchtronic ControlsCondensor Container (click for details)Fault Indicators - the smart Novotronic controls continuously monitor both the intake lines and drain lines. The indicator lights will advise you if a problem is detected.PC Update Function - you can now keep up with technological advances. For example, using a laptop computer, a Miele technician can alter a machine's programming parameters to reduce its water intake or electricity consumption or even adapt it to a new type of detergent.Miele Interior Light (click for details)220 voltsChild lock featureSelf-diagnosticsOptional laundry stand available (see below)Drying Programs2 Moisture-based, standard drying programs4 Moisture-based, specialty drying programs2 timed, drying programsTurbo drying optionFull l", "labels": [[0, 31, "ORG"], [33, 46, "ORG"], [87, 88, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [126, 127, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [143, 154, "PRODUCT"], [219, 267, "ORG"], [279, 292, "ORG"], [316, 326, "ORG"], [436, 437, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [547, 548, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [566, 567, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [568, 573, "BRAND"], [595, 596, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [704, 705, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [728, 733, "BRAND"], [772, 782, "PERSON"], [947, 956, "ORG"], [971, 984, "ORG"]]}
{"text": "Quality always comes from dedication. We think you'll fall in love withAsko's appliances at first sight. However, that initial spark will soon develop into a steady relationship, and then you'll find out whether the inside is everything the outside promises.The way we see it, your appliances should last for a long time. That's exactly whattheir designers aim for as they meticulously analyse every detail. And the results are amazing. They have been producing household appliances for over half a century, and year after yearthey have seen how sturdy wins over thin, simple over complicated and steel over plastic. Time after time, quality has paid off! Get something extra! Whatever can't be dried in the dryer goes into the drying cabinet where a gentle heat speeds the drying process. Never again will you have clothes drying on doorknobs, shower rods, counter tops or", "labels": [[92, 97, "ORDINAL"], [156, 157, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [309, 310, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [497, 498, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [617, 621, "ORG"], [749, 750, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"]]}
{"text": "Avanti W798SS Washer W798SS Portable Washer and Dryer", "labels": [[0, 6, "ORG"]]}
{"text": "Keep your clothes looking like new with this dryer that utilizes Sensor Dry to monitor dampness levels, ensuring your clothes are completely dry without causing unnecessary wear and tear.", "labels": [[65, 75, "PRODUCT"]]}
{"text": "DROP SHIP ONLY!!!  This 3.8 cu. ft. capacity washer features Direct Inject spot and stain removal, variable spin speeds and Quiet Wash Plus sound reduction.  Color: white on white", "labels": [[24, 30, "QUANTITY"], [61, 74, "ORG"], [124, 139, "PRODUCT"]]}
{"text": "Auto dry. Four heat selections. Three drying cycles. Rotary mechanical controls. Upfront lint filter. 33-1/4\" H x 24-1/2\" D x 23-7/8\" W. White.", "labels": [[10, 14, "CARDINAL"], [32, 37, "CARDINAL"], [102, 104, "CARDINAL"], [114, 116, "CARDINAL"], [122, 123, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [126, 128, "CARDINAL"]]}
{"text": "If you're looking for the perfect balance of performance, efficiency and convenience, you'll find it with the GE Profile Harmony(TM) laundry pair. The HydroWash(TM) system takes top load wash technology to new heights, gently cleaning all types of fabrics-from special synthetic materials to delicate lingerie. And the StainInspector(TM) system treats more than 80 stains,* from grass marks to grease. When you're in a hurry, the DuoDry(TM) system keeps pace, drying clothes in the same time it takes to wash them. Best of all, getting superior results is simple. That's because once you program the washer, there's no need to select cycles for the dryer. All you have to do is press, Start. The Harmony Washer offers a king-size, 4.0 cu ft. stainless steel basket, making it one of the largest-capacity washers available. Making room for more items means less time doing", "labels": [[110, 112, "BRAND"], [352, 364, "CARDINAL"], [417, 418, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [696, 710, "ORG"], [718, 719, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [731, 740, "QUANTITY"], [776, 779, "CARDINAL"]]}
{"text": "Nexxt 500 Series Gas", "labels": []}
{"text": "LG's innovative SteamFresh cycle makes it possible for you to refresh and reduce wrinkles in up to 5 garments at one time.Running late for work with no time to iron? Load a cotton blend shirt and select the SteamFresh cycle.You'll be ready to go in just 20 minutes.Neutralizes static electricity in normal loads by introducing steam during the final five minutes of the cycle.Evenly and lightly moistens load prior to cycle end.Intuitive controls allow you to 'set it and go'.You can also save your favorite dry cycle by pressing Custom Program.You'll have optimized drying performance with the push of a button.The dryer's dual humidity sensors detect moisture in the load and adjust the drying time accordingly.This keeps you from under or overdrying your clothes, and ensures optimal drying performance.LG's Remote Monitoring System makes it easier to keep tabs on your laundry.Simply plug the modem into any outlet", "labels": [[0, 2, "BRAND"], [16, 26, "ORG"], [93, 100, "CARDINAL"], [113, 116, "CARDINAL"], [171, 172, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [207, 217, "ORG"], [249, 264, "TIME"], [340, 362, "TIME"], [530, 544, "ORG"], [545, 551, "ORG"], [603, 604, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [806, 808, "BRAND"], [811, 835, "ORG"]]}
{"text": "25\" Top-Load AquaSmart Washer with 3.7 cu. ft. Capacity, 10 Wash Cycles, 1,000 RPM Spin Speed, Bleach Dispenser, Touch Control Panel with LCD Screen and Load Sensing", "labels": [[0, 2, "CARDINAL"], [35, 41, "QUANTITY"], [57, 59, "CARDINAL"], [60, 71, "ORG"], [73, 78, "CARDINAL"], [79, 93, "ORG"], [95, 111, "ORG"], [113, 132, "ORG"], [138, 148, "ORG"], [153, 165, "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "Extra Large 2.5 Cu. Ft. CapacitySpreckle Porcelain Basket4 CyclesHeavy Duty CyclePermanent Press Cycle1 Temperature Setting1-Piece Agitator1 Wash/Spin Speed Combination4 Water Level SelectionsDimensions: (HWD) 42 x 27 x 25 In.", "labels": [[12, 18, "QUANTITY"], [51, 58, "PERSON"], [205, 208, "ORG"], [210, 212, "CARDINAL"], [215, 217, "CARDINAL"], [220, 222, "CARDINAL"]]}
{"text": "GE WCVH6260F Energy Star 3.7 IEC Cu. Ft. King-size Capacity Frontload Washer with Stainless Steel", "labels": [[0, 2, "BRAND"], [25, 28, "CARDINAL"], [29, 32, "ORG"], [51, 76, "ORG"], [82, 97, "ORG"]]}
{"text": "The GEWVSR1060GWWutilizes an easy to use rotary electronic control system with six wash cycles ideal for anyone with a variety washing needs. The super large capacity enables this machine to hold up to 3.2 cu. ft. of laundry. It also boasts the FlexCare agitator, which cleans clothes more without damaging them, a must have feature on any washing machine. Lastly the Quiet-By-Design sound inulation system ensues sleeping will not be disurbed by this model. A great model for any home.", "labels": [[79, 82, "CARDINAL"], [117, 118, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [202, 208, "QUANTITY"], [245, 253, "ORG"], [313, 314, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [459, 460, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"]]}
{"text": "3.6 Cu. Ft. Capacity3 Dry Cycles: Cottons - Automatic Regular, Timed Dry (150 Mins.) and Quick Fluff (no heat) - 30 Mins.3 Heat Selections (Timer)DuraDrum InteriorQuiet-By-Design", "labels": [[0, 6, "QUANTITY"], [63, 72, "ORG"], [74, 77, "CARDINAL"], [113, 115, "CARDINAL"], [123, 138, "ORG"], [155, 168, "ORG"]]}
{"text": "Ne xx t 100 Series Washer", "labels": [[0, 7, "PERSON"], [8, 11, "CARDINAL"]]}
{"text": "27\" Top-Load Dryer with 6.2 cu. ft. Capacity, 10 Cycles, Reverse Tumbling and Autosensing Drying: Electric", "labels": [[0, 2, "CARDINAL"], [4, 18, "ORG"], [24, 30, "QUANTITY"], [46, 48, "CARDINAL"]]}
{"text": "The LG WM3431HW Washer Dryer Combo is EnergyStar rated and achieved CEE Tier 3B for energy efficiency! Although combo washer dryers are generally more energy efficient than standard washers and dryers, this unit is particularly notable for its energy and water efficiency. Also, because it is EnergyStar rated, it may be eligible for rebates from your local utility companies. Check with your local water and power companies for more details.This unit offers a 2.44 Capacity, direct drive drum which minimizes the noise and vibration that other washer dryer combos can produce. This unit also comes with an internal water heater.Unlike most washer dryers, which require you to guess how much drying is needed, the LG WM3431HW combo washer dryer has a sensor that monitors the dryness of your clothes. When your clothes are bone-dry, the cycle stops- and the cool down mode tumbles your clothes without heat for hours after the cycle is over to prevent wrinkles from setting in!", "labels": [[4, 6, "BRAND"], [38, 48, "ORG"], [68, 76, "PERSON"], [77, 79, "PRODUCT"], [293, 303, "ORG"], [459, 460, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [461, 465, "CARDINAL"], [714, 716, "BRAND"], [749, 750, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [911, 916, "TIME"]]}
{"text": "XL Load Capacity with NeveRust Stainless Steel Drum (7.3 cu.ft. IEC)LoDecibel Quiet System (58dB sound power)Fast Drying TimeSensor Dry System for intelligent fabric care and energy efficiency9 Drying Programs5 Temperature LevelsPrecise Temperature Control with a variable heat sourceDrying RackWrinkle Care OptionDelicate and Ultra Delicate CycleDamp Dry BeeperCustom ProgramUpfront Electronic Control with Dial-A-CycleLarge Chrome Rimmed Door with Clear GlassPorcelain TopOptional Drawer PedestalsDimensions: (WHD) 27 x 42 3/4 x 28 1/3 In.", "labels": [[0, 21, "ORG"], [22, 51, "PRODUCT"], [53, 56, "CARDINAL"], [57, 62, "ORG"], [78, 90, "ORG"], [92, 96, "CARDINAL"], [121, 142, "ORG"], [262, 263, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [291, 307, "PERSON"], [327, 351, "ORG"], [356, 402, "ORG"], [413, 414, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [512, 515, "ORG"], [517, 519, "CARDINAL"], [522, 528, "CARDINAL"], [531, 533, "CARDINAL"], [534, 537, "CARDINAL"]]}
{"text": "Type Front Loader Yes Design Look Front Control Intelligent Electronic Controls With Dial-a-cycle&trade; Yes Capacity Iec 4.2 Cu.ft. Dry Linen Capacity >10.1 Kg Energy Energy Star Compliant Yes Wash Programs 9 Programs Sanitary (158&deg; f), Bulky/large, Perm Press, Cotton/normal, Baby Wear, Delicates, Hand Wash/wool, Speed Wash, Drain + Spin 5 Wash/rinse Temps Extra Hot/cold, Hot/cold, Warm/warm, Warm/cold, Cold/cold Spin Speeds Extra High (1200 Max), High (1000), Medium (980/780/600), Low (950/600/400), No Spin No. Of Water Levels Automatically Adjusts To Size Of Load No. Of Soil Level 5 10 Options Prewash, Rinse + Spin, Extra Rinse, Stain Cycle, Water Plus, Tub Clean, Load Sensing Indicator, Spinsense,custom Program, Delay Wash (up To 19 Hours) Fabric Care Features Senseclean&trade; System Yes Rollerjets&trade; Yes Convenience Features 4 Tray Dispenser Prewash, Main Wash (with Liquid Detergent Cup), Bleach, Softener End Of Cycle Beeper Yes Child Lock Yes Self-diagnosis Yes Auto Balancing Yes Load Sense Yes Auto Suds Removal Yes Forced Drain System Yes Status Indicator(s) Yes Internal Water Heater (1000w) Yes Leveling Legs 4 Adjustable Legs Lodecibel&trade; Quiet Operation Yes Motor And Agitator Motor Type / Motor Speed / Axis Direct Drive / Variable / Horizontal Materials And Finishes Neverust&trade; Stainless Steel Drum Yes Easy Loading Tiltub&trade; Yes Cabinet Painted Steel Control Panel Plastic Top Plate Painted Transparent Door Glass Yes Door Rim Chrome Available Colors White (w), Pearl Gray (g) Power Source Ratings / Electrical Requirements / Type Ul Listed / 120v, 10 Amps / Electric Options Pedestal Wdp3w, Wdp3g (drawer With Handle) Pedestal (wxhxd) 27\" X 13 3/5\" X 28 2/5\" Stacking Kit Wstk1, Rstk1 Dimensions Product (wxhxd) 27\" X 38 11/16\" X 29 3/4\"(51\"d With Door Open) Carton (wxhxd) 29 1/2\" X 43 5/16\" X 31 5/16\" Product Weight / Shipping Weight 192 / 216 Warranty Limited Warranty 90 Days From Refurbking Inc.", "labels": [[90, 91, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [153, 157, "CARDINAL"], [208, 209, "CARDINAL"], [238, 239, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [255, 265, "ORG"], [267, 280, "ORG"], [282, 291, "ORG"], [293, 302, "ORG"], [304, 313, "ORG"], [320, 330, "GPE"], [332, 344, "ORG"], [345, 346, "CARDINAL"], [446, 450, "CARDINAL"], [451, 454, "PERSON"], [463, 467, "CARDINAL"], [478, 489, "CARDINAL"], [497, 508, "CARDINAL"], [584, 594, "GPE"], [595, 599, "TIME"], [617, 629, "LAW"], [631, 642, "PRODUCT"], [644, 655, "PRODUCT"], [657, 667, "PRODUCT"], [669, 678, "ORG"], [680, 702, "ORG"], [704, 713, "PRODUCT"], [721, 728, "ORG"], [730, 740, "PERSON"], [742, 756, "TIME"], [893, 913, "EVENT"], [916, 922, "PERSON"], [924, 952, "ORG"], [1178, 1193, "ORG"], [1208, 1263, "ORG"], [1325, 1345, "ORG"], [1377, 1442, "ORG"], [1460, 1465, "PERSON"], [1514, 1524, "PERSON"], [1526, 1527, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [1595, 1599, "PRODUCT"], [1601, 1603, "CARDINAL"], [1648, 1649, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [1688, 1690, "CARDINAL"], [1694, 1700, "CARDINAL"], [1704, 1710, "CARDINAL"], [1712, 1724, "ORG"], [1765, 1767, "DATE"], [1771, 1779, "CARDINAL"], [1783, 1785, "CARDINAL"], [1827, 1833, "CARDINAL"], [1837, 1844, "CARDINAL"], [1848, 1855, "CARDINAL"], [1857, 1889, "WORK_OF_ART"], [1926, 1933, "DATE"], [1939, 1954, "ORG"]]}
{"text": "This is a genuine replacement part. The model number and name for the following item is: Stacking Kit 5303937141 Frigidaire bracket flange this is a staking kit for front loading washers", "labels": [[8, 9, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [113, 123, "BRAND"], [147, 148, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"]]}
{"text": "This all-in-one laundry center features a Precision Wash system and a Balanced Dry system for custom laundry care. A host of easy-to-use washing and drying functions help you launder sweaters, jeans and heavy comforters with ease.", "labels": [[12, 15, "CARDINAL"], [40, 41, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [42, 56, "ORG"], [68, 69, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [70, 82, "ORG"], [115, 116, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"]]}
{"text": "Super CapacityExtended Venting CapabilityAdjustable Degree of Dryness with Sensor Dry CycleFlexible ConfigurationLarge Lint ScreenControl LockoutMultiple CyclesWrinkle Release CycleSofSound IIIWrinkle Prevent CycleCool Down Indicator LightElectronic Controls with Cycle Indicator LightsAffordable StyleAir Fluff CycleDelicate DryOn/Off End-of-Cycle SignalOptional Storage PedestalReversible-Swing DoorTimed Dry CycleNumber of Cycles: 6Temperature Settings: 3Sensor DryTimed Dry: Adjustable, 0-99 min.Delicate DryAir FluffWrinkle ReleaseWrinkle PreventRegular DryElectric Controls with Cycle Indicator LightsOn/Off End-of-Cycle SignalReversible-Swing Door (no kit required)Powdercoat TopControl LockoutSound Package: SofSound IIIExtended Venting Capability: Up to 80'Large Lint Screen: 77 sq. in.Height: 38Width: 27Depth: 28 3/4Depth with Door Open 90 Degrees: 46 7/16", "labels": [[62, 69, "LOC"], [465, 473, "PERSON"], [491, 499, "TIME"], [656, 714, "ORG"], [716, 755, "ORG"], [763, 771, "CARDINAL"], [772, 776, "PERSON"], [785, 790, "QUANTITY"], [795, 801, "PERSON"], [821, 832, "CARDINAL"], [848, 858, "QUANTITY"], [860, 867, "CARDINAL"]]}
{"text": "Antimicrobial Component ProtectionMultiple CyclesENERGY STAR QualifiedFlexible ConfigurationSuper CapacityVariable Water LevelsAutomatic Temperature ControlAdjustable Soil LevelsSofSound IIIStainless Steel Wash TubElectronic Controls with Cycle Indicator LightsAffordable StyleDelay Wash OptionDelicates CycleDetergent, Bleach and Fabric Softener DispensersElectronic Controls with Cycle Indicator LightsEnd-of-Cycle SignalExtra Rinse OptionHandwash CycleOptional Storage PedestalQuick Wash CycleReversible-Swing DoorRinse and Spin OptionSpin Only OptionSuper Wash CycleWrinkle Control CycleNumber of Cycles: 8Super Wash CycleQuick Wash CycleDelicates CycleHandwash CycleWrinkle Control CycleDelay Wash OptionExtra Rinse OptionRinse and Spin OptionSpin Only OptionAdjustable Soil Level: Heavy, Medium and LightWater Levels: Auto FillWater Temperatures: 5Automatic Temperature ControlSpeed Combinations: 4Electronic Controls with Cycle Indicator LightsEnd-of-Cycle SignalDispensers: Detergent, Bleach and Fabric SoftnerPowerdercoat TopStainless Steel Wash TubControl LockoutHeight: 38 In.Width: 27 In.Depth: 30 3/4 In.Depth with Door Open 90 Degrees: 46 7/16 In.", "labels": [[320, 397, "ORG"], [609, 615, "CARDINAL"], [616, 636, "ORG"], [903, 914, "CARDINAL"], [915, 980, "ORG"], [993, 999, "PERSON"], [1081, 1083, "CARDINAL"], [1094, 1096, "CARDINAL"], [1107, 1113, "CARDINAL"], [1138, 1148, "QUANTITY"], [1150, 1157, "CARDINAL"]]}
{"text": "EPICz Front Load Washer", "labels": [[0, 23, "ORG"]]}
{"text": "White with Chrome Accents 3.8 cu.ft. Capacity German Engineered Duet HT(R) super capacity Front-Loading Washer", "labels": [[11, 35, "PRODUCT"], [46, 52, "NORP"], [90, 110, "PRODUCT"]]}
{"text": "Power Cord and Venting Sold Separately7.0 Cu. Ft. Super Capacity Plus DrumAccelerCare Drying System7 Automatic CyclesTimed DryingQuick Dry CycleWrinkle Shield Plus Feature (60 Minutes)5 Temperature SelectionsQuiet Dry Noise ReductionInterior Drum LightDimensions: (WHD) 29 x 36 x 27 13/16 In.", "labels": [[0, 10, "ORG"], [42, 44, "PERSON"], [173, 175, "CARDINAL"], [265, 268, "ORG"], [270, 272, "CARDINAL"], [275, 277, "CARDINAL"], [280, 288, "CARDINAL"]]}
{"text": "&lt;li&gt; ENERGY STAR Qualified&lt;li&gt; Direct Inject Wash System&lt;li&gt; 6th Sense Technology&lt;li&gt; Stainless Steel Wash Drum&lt;li&gt; Care Control Temperature Management&lt;li&gt; 5 Temperature Selections&lt;li&gt; Automatic Water Level Settings&lt;li&gt; 11 Automatic Cycles&lt;li&gt; Bulky Items Cycle&lt;li&gt; Clean Washer Cycle&lt;li&gt; Woolmark Certified Wool Cycle&lt;li&gt; Dimensions: (WHD) 28 x 42 x 27 In.", "labels": [[43, 61, "ORG"], [79, 82, "ORDINAL"], [110, 144, "ORG"], [146, 170, "ORG"], [192, 193, "CARDINAL"], [194, 205, "PRODUCT"], [227, 248, "PERSON"], [268, 270, "CARDINAL"], [271, 280, "ORG"], [326, 338, "PRODUCT"], [355, 378, "ORG"], [408, 411, "ORG"], [413, 415, "CARDINAL"], [418, 420, "CARDINAL"], [423, 425, "CARDINAL"]]}
{"text": "Silver Metallic on White Whirlpool(R) Duet(R) Steam Washer", "labels": [[0, 15, "ORG"]]}
{"text": "&lt;li&gt; Assigns wash action - Assigns wash action, from gentle to heavy duty, based on load size and composition&lt;li&gt; Cleans fabrics - Moves clothes through a concentrated detergent shower in a blossoming motion&lt;li&gt; Direct inject wash system - The revolutionary Direct Inject wash system deep cleans large loads with a stain-removing shower of concentrated detergent, virtually eliminating the need for pre-treating&lt;li&gt; High-efficiency design - Not only will you save time doing laundry, you&apos;ll also save precious resources. Compared to the other top-load washers, this Cabrio washer uses less water and 55 percent less energy&lt;li&gt; Woolmark certified wool cycle - This Cabrio washer&apos;s wool cycle is certified by Woolmark for the extra delicate care of washable wools&lt;li&gt; Variable motor speeds&lt;li&gt; Stainless steel wash drum&lt;li&gt; Care control temperature management&lt;li&gt; 5 temperatures&lt;li&gt; 10 cycles&lt;li&gt; Automatic water levels&lt;li&gt; Bulky items cycle&lt;li&gt; Clean washer cycle&lt;li&gt; Whitest white cycle&lt;li&gt; Quick wash cycle&lt;li&gt; Deep clean option&lt;li&gt; Detergent, Bleach and Fabric softener automatic dispensers&lt;li&gt; Up to 950 RPM maximum spin speed&lt;li&gt; Add-a-Garment indicator&lt;li&gt; Safety lock&lt;li&gt; Estimated time remaining display&lt;li&gt; Ultra Quiet wash plus noise reduction system&lt;li&gt; Energy Star qualified model&lt;li&gt; Dimensions: (WHD) 28 x 42 x 27 In.", "labels": [[11, 18, "PERSON"], [165, 166, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [200, 201, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [276, 289, "ORG"], [331, 332, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [508, 519, "ORG"], [595, 601, "ORG"], [629, 639, "PERCENT"], [662, 670, "PERSON"], [747, 755, "GPE"], [844, 853, "ORG"], [880, 884, "ORG"], [926, 927, "CARDINAL"], [951, 953, "CARDINAL"], [971, 980, "NORP"], [1118, 1122, "PERSON"], [1146, 1155, "ORG"], [1157, 1174, "ORG"], [1215, 1224, "CARDINAL"], [1225, 1228, "ORG"], [1262, 1263, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [1357, 1368, "ORG"], [1412, 1423, "ORG"], [1450, 1460, "ORG"], [1463, 1466, "ORG"], [1468, 1470, "CARDINAL"], [1473, 1475, "CARDINAL"], [1478, 1480, "CARDINAL"]]}
{"text": "Silver Metallic on White Whirlpool(R) Duet(R) Steam Electric Dryer", "labels": [[0, 15, "ORG"], [46, 66, "ORG"]]}
{"text": "Bleach Dispenser14 CyclesDelicate CycleVariable End-of-Cycle SignalENERGY STAR QualifiedExtra Rinse OptionFabric Softener DispenserHandwashable CycleHeavy Duty CycleLint FilterVariable MotorPrewash CycleQuick WashQuiet Wash Plus Sound PackageSound Reduction5 Temperature SettingsDirect Inject Wash System5 Wash/Spin SpeedsAUTOMATIC Water Level SelectionsWool CycleSanitary Cycle: The internal water heater warms the wash water to 153 degrees F., a temperature hot enough to eliminate 99.999% of harmful bacteria. Use of the sanitary cycle can eliminate the need for bleach to disinfect and sanitize certain types of laundrySilk CycleWhitest Whites Cycle: Heated wash water, coupled with the accuracy of the Smart Bleach dispensing system, helps ensure loads of whites receive optimal cleaning performanceWool CycleAdjustable", "labels": [[0, 60, "ORG"], [160, 169, "ORG"], [198, 208, "ORG"], [293, 305, "PERSON"], [430, 441, "QUANTITY"], [446, 447, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [484, 491, "PERCENT"], [628, 654, "ORG"], [707, 719, "ORG"], [809, 824, "ORG"]]}
{"text": "GE Consumer &amp; Industrial spans the globe as an industry leader in major appliance, lighting and integrated industrial equipment systems and services. They provide solutions for commercial, industrial and residential use in more than 100 countries which uses innovative technologies and  ecomagination.  It&apos;s a GE initiative to aggressively bring to market new technologies that help customers and consumers meet pressing environmental challenges to deliver comfort, convenience and electrical protection and control. GE brings imagination to work.    This model features a super plus ExtrAction wash basket which offers increased surface area to  squeeze  more water from clothes during the spin cycle resulting in reduced dry times. The HydroWave wash system delivers thorough, yet complete gentle cleaning performance. It&apos;s a 360 degree stroke of the agitator which moves clothes through the water slowly in a smooth wave like agitation. 24 wash cycles give you a greater control over laundry results. The built in bleach and fabric softener dispensers eliminates much of the hassle involved with doing the laundry. Don&apos;t worry about trying to get to sleep with this model running, the Quiet-By-Design sound insulation system greatly reduces the noise it makes.", "labels": [[0, 2, "BRAND"], [227, 240, "CARDINAL"], [317, 318, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [319, 321, "BRAND"], [526, 528, "BRAND"], [580, 581, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [593, 603, "ORG"], [747, 756, "ORG"], [840, 841, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [842, 852, "QUANTITY"], [924, 925, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [954, 956, "CARDINAL"], [978, 979, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [1132, 1142, "CARDINAL"], [1203, 1222, "WORK_OF_ART"]]}
{"text": "28\" Top-Load Washer with 4.6 cu. ft. Capacity, 11 Automatic Wash Cycles, 5 Temperature Settings, QuietSeries 600 Sound Package and Clear See-Through Lid: White", "labels": [[0, 2, "CARDINAL"], [25, 31, "QUANTITY"], [47, 49, "CARDINAL"], [50, 71, "ORG"], [73, 74, "CARDINAL"]]}
{"text": "WSLP1100HWW - GE Spacemaker(R) Extra-Large Capacity Portable Washer with Stainless Steel Basket", "labels": [[14, 16, "BRAND"], [73, 88, "ORG"]]}
{"text": "The power of TrueSteam penetrates fabrics for optimal cleaning performance and also reduces allergens by more than 95% with LGs exclusive Allergiene cycle.AllergieneAllergiene cycle is proven to reduce certain allergens such as house dust mites and domestic animal dander.SteamFreshLG's innovative SteamFresh cycle makes it possible for you to refresh and reduce wrinkles in up to 5 garments at one time. Running late for work with no time to iron? Load a cotton blend shirt into the SteamWasher and select the SteamFresh cycle. You'll be ready to go in just 20 minutes.Intelligent Electronic Controls with Dual LED Display and Dial-A-CycleIntuitive controls take the guesswork out of doing laundry allowing you to 'set it and go'.Remote Monitor ReadyLG's Remote Monitoring System makes it easier to keep tabs on your laundry. Simply plug the modem into any outlet in your home and it communicates with the machine to display the time remaining in the cycle. Whether you're putting away groceries or relaxing with a good book, you'll know how much time is left. Your repeated trips to the laundry room are over.Side by Side or Stacked?Your Choice. Less space? Try stacking the washer and dryer.  More space? Place them side by side or under a counter.  Dont want to bend down so far to load or unload clothing?  Add our 13.7\" high drawer pedestals. They're also a greatplace to store laundry products.", "labels": [[13, 22, "ORG"], [105, 118, "PERCENT"], [138, 148, "ORG"], [155, 175, "ORG"], [298, 308, "ORG"], [375, 382, "CARDINAL"], [395, 398, "CARDINAL"], [454, 455, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [484, 495, "ORG"], [511, 521, "ORG"], [554, 569, "TIME"], [570, 601, "ORG"], [607, 615, "ORG"], [633, 634, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [756, 780, "ORG"], [1014, 1015, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [1127, 1146, "ORG"], [1241, 1242, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [1320, 1324, "QUANTITY"], [1362, 1363, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"]]}
{"text": "White-on-White 7.0 cu.ft Duet(R) High Efficiency Gas Dryer", "labels": [[15, 18, "CARDINAL"], [19, 24, "ORG"], [33, 58, "ORG"]]}
{"text": "Topload Rear Control Washer Replaces: AWS45. Commercial Built Transmission. Hush Pak. 3.3 cu. ft. Stainless Steel Wash Tub. Galvanized Metal Washer Cabinet. High Speed Water Extraction. Automatic Balancing System. View Control Panel. 210(degree) Agitation Stroke. Variable Water Selection.", "labels": [[0, 20, "ORG"], [45, 74, "ORG"], [86, 92, "QUANTITY"], [98, 122, "ORG"], [141, 155, "ORG"], [162, 184, "ORG"], [186, 212, "ORG"], [214, 232, "ORG"], [234, 244, "CARDINAL"]]}
{"text": "24\" Front Load High Efficiency Axxis Washer - WAS20160UC", "labels": [[0, 2, "CARDINAL"]]}
{"text": "Drum capacity: 7.0 cu. ft.Dryer control: AccelerCare drying systemTemperature options: 5 temperature selectionsType of controls: electronic/rotary controlsVentilation features: 4-way ventingCabinet: front access with reversible door with easy view windowAir Filtration: front-mounted lint screenWrinkle prevention: wrinkle shield plus feature (140 minutes)Cycles: bulky items, damp dry, delicate, quick dry, cool down, extended tumbling, steam refresh, extra dryAdjustable end-of-cycle signalQuiet dry plus noise reductionDry rackInterior drum lightAudio feedbackInstructional controlsFlexible installation with matching washerPowder coat drum materialAuto dry controlElectronic sensor drying1/3 HP motorY-adapter includedDryer cord is not included. Sold separately in 3 or 4 prong.Dimensions: 27.0\" W x 38.0\" H x 31.5\" DWeight: appro", "labels": [[0, 4, "ORG"], [15, 21, "QUANTITY"], [41, 52, "ORG"], [60, 77, "GPE"], [87, 88, "CARDINAL"], [289, 302, "CARDINAL"], [344, 347, "CARDINAL"], [486, 497, "NORP"], [621, 633, "ORG"], [661, 678, "GPE"], [686, 713, "PRODUCT"], [769, 781, "QUANTITY"], [794, 798, "CARDINAL"], [804, 808, "CARDINAL"], [814, 818, "CARDINAL"]]}
{"text": "7.0 cu. ft. Electric Dryer - Front Control - Silver Door Trim - White", "labels": [[0, 6, "QUANTITY"], [12, 56, "ORG"]]}
{"text": "This top-load washer is 62% more energy efficient and 52% more water efficient than the minimum Energy Star rating. Plus, wash  three baskets of laundry in a single load, thanks to a 4.5 cu. ft. I.E.C. capacity. And with the Direct Inject wash system, a burst of detergent penetrates stains and stubborn soil so you don&apos;t have to pretreat.", "labels": [[24, 27, "PERCENT"], [54, 57, "PERCENT"], [96, 107, "ORG"], [128, 133, "CARDINAL"], [156, 157, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [181, 182, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [183, 189, "QUANTITY"], [225, 238, "ORG"], [252, 253, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [316, 326, "PRODUCT"]]}
{"text": "This Affinity Front Load Washer features a chrome trim, electronic control panel, iCare ultra intelligent fabric care, iWash ultra intelligent fabric care, king-size 3. 5 cu ft capacity, and silent design for whisper-quiet operation. Addition features include: 7 Wash cycles, built-in water heather, heavy/light soil options, tumble action cleaning system, 17 hour delay start, estimated time remaining indicator. Color: Black Diamond. Unit Dimensions (in Inches): 27 W x 36 H x 27 D. This is a special order item. It CAN NOT be cancelled once ordered.", "labels": [[0, 31, "ORG"], [41, 42, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [82, 87, "ORG"], [166, 167, "CARDINAL"], [169, 170, "CARDINAL"], [261, 262, "CARDINAL"], [357, 364, "TIME"], [465, 467, "CARDINAL"], [472, 474, "CARDINAL"], [479, 481, "CARDINAL"], [493, 494, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"]]}
{"text": "LG s revolutionary front-load SteamWasher washing machine lets you kiss stains goodbye along with 95 of pet dander, dust mites, and other common allergens. What s more, the unique LG steam generator penetrates fabrics, for enhanced cleaning performance. (Capacity: 4. 2 cu. Ft. ) One of the largest front-load washers available-4. 2 cu. Ft. Capacity. Less coughs and sneezes The Allergiene cycle uses the power of steam to gently remove over 95 of common common household allergens, like dust mites and pet dander, from even the most delicate fabrics. Now doing the laundry can save some sniffles. 1100 RPM maximum spin for efficient water extraction. Generates real steam to reduce wrinkles and odors, and practically eliminate the need for ironing. This revolutionary washing system uses LG s TrueSteam generator to boost cleaning performance and energy efficiency. Energy Star Rated. Red Finish", "labels": [[0, 2, "BRAND"], [30, 41, "ORG"], [98, 100, "CARDINAL"], [180, 182, "BRAND"], [265, 266, "CARDINAL"], [268, 272, "QUANTITY"], [280, 283, "CARDINAL"], [331, 335, "QUANTITY"], [379, 389, "LOC"], [437, 444, "CARDINAL"], [598, 602, "CARDINAL"], [603, 606, "PERSON"], [790, 792, "BRAND"], [795, 804, "PRODUCT"], [868, 885, "ORG"]]}
{"text": "&lt;li&gt; King-Size 3.5 cu. ft. I.E.C. Capacity&lt;li&gt; Stainless Steel Wash Drum&lt;li&gt; Electronic Controls&lt;li&gt; Tumble Action Cleaning System&lt;li&gt; 14 Wash Cycles&lt;li&gt; Cycle Status Lights&lt;li&gt; On/Off End-of-Cycle Signal&lt;li&gt; Heavy/Light Soil Options&lt;li&gt; Advanced Rinse Technology&lt;li&gt; Extra Rinse &amp; Extra Spin Auto Options&lt;li&gt; Adjustable 12-Hour Delay Start&lt;li&gt; Estimated Time Remaining Indicator&lt;li&gt; Press Saver Setting&lt;li&gt; Control Lock&lt;li&gt; Door Lock Light&lt;li&gt; Optional Pedestal NLPWD15 Available&lt;li&gt; Width: 27&quot;&lt;li&gt; Height: 36&quot;&lt;li&gt; Depth: 27 3/4&quot;", "labels": [[11, 20, "ORG"], [21, 27, "QUANTITY"], [59, 93, "ORG"], [125, 147, "ORG"], [165, 167, "CARDINAL"], [257, 273, "LAW"], [292, 306, "PRODUCT"], [334, 341, "ORG"], [346, 361, "ORG"], [380, 419, "PRODUCT"], [431, 464, "ORG"], [466, 477, "ORG"], [496, 517, "ORG"], [524, 528, "ORG"], [617, 623, "PERSON"], [644, 649, "PERSON"], [651, 653, "CARDINAL"]]}
{"text": "10 Cycle Front Load Washer", "labels": [[0, 2, "CARDINAL"]]}
{"text": "Dry and dewrinkle your clothes all in one machine with this super capacity dryer. It features a precision-dry moisture sensor to properly dry clothing and an auto press-saver function that reduces wrinkles and cuts down on ironing.", "labels": [[38, 41, "CARDINAL"], [94, 95, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"]]}
{"text": "5.8 Cu. Ft. Super Capacity DrumElectronic Control PaneliCare Intelligent Fabric CareiDry Intelligent Fabric Care7 Auto Dry Cycles4 Dryness Level Selections90 Minute Timed DryAuto Shrink Guard OptionControl LockCycle Status LightsDrying RackPrecision Dry Moisture SensorTumble Care Drying SystemAuto Press Saver OptionEstimated Time Remaining IndicatorInterior Drum LightReversible DoorClean Lint Filter IndicatorQuick-Clean Lint Screen", "labels": [[0, 6, "QUANTITY"], [12, 49, "ORG"], [114, 130, "PRODUCT"]]}
{"text": "mfr: Bosch 3.81 cu.ft. capacity, ENERGY STAR, 15 washing programs, JEANS cycle, COMFORTER cycle, REFRESH cycle, XXTRASanitary 170 degrees 99.99% bacterail elimination, AQUAGuard water proofing, Quick wash option, spin speed up to 1200 rpm, 54 dB quiet operation, 24 hour time delay, ECO-Option, rinse plus, heavy duty, child lock-out feature, pre-soak function&lt;br&gt;Special Order, this items ships in 2 to 3 weeks", "labels": [[5, 10, "BRAND"], [16, 21, "ORG"], [46, 48, "CARDINAL"], [80, 89, "ORG"], [230, 234, "CARDINAL"], [240, 242, "DATE"], [263, 270, "TIME"], [283, 293, "ORG"], [378, 383, "PRODUCT"], [405, 417, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Rotary electronic controls are simple to use; LED indicators let you know the settings at a glance7.0 cu. ft. super capacity can take on large loads, so you can dry bulky items without making a trip to the laundromatMultiple cycles include speed dry, dewrinkle, cottons, delicates, easy care, mixed loads, timed dry and extended tumbleSensor Dry continually monitors moisture levels to keep your clothes looking newer longer; 4 heat selections let you customize each load to fit the needs of different fabric typesDual thermistors maintain consistent heat, ensuring the right level of dryness is reached; optional dryness levels let you adjust the degree of dryness obtainedDelay-start feature lets you program the dryer to work in your absence, so you can take advantage of reduced electrical ratesLint filter reminder light will let you know when it's time to clean the filter, so the dryer will continue to perform at optimal levels; interior", "labels": [[0, 6, "ORG"], [90, 91, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [192, 193, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [206, 224, "ORG"], [329, 345, "ORG"], [426, 427, "CARDINAL"]]}
{"text": "&lt;li&gt; King-size, 3.5-cu.-ft.  stainless steel basket makes room for more items, which means less time doing laundry&lt;li&gt; HydroWave wash system  Has variable speeds to match the wash action to the clothing type. Longer, slower travel through the water improves cleaning performance and is gentler on your clothes&lt;li&gt; Five wash/spin speed combinations  Speeds are matched to fabric type for better clothes care&lt;li&gt; 18 wash cycles  A cycle for all of your laundry loads and needs&lt;li&gt; Four wash/rinse temperatures  Washer cleans at the exact temperature needed to remove dirt and reduce wear&lt;li&gt; Four water levels  Offers water and energy savings&lt;li&gt; Prewash Cycle  Allows clothing additional time to soak and agitate to help remove stubborn stains", "labels": [[131, 140, "ORG"], [332, 336, "CARDINAL"], [435, 437, "CARDINAL"], [451, 452, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [509, 513, "CARDINAL"], [539, 545, "NORP"], [626, 630, "CARDINAL"], [687, 700, "PRODUCT"]]}
{"text": "&lt;li&gt; Senseon Drying System gently dries clothes in the time it takes to wash them&lt;li&gt; Cycle choices for all fabric needs&lt;li&gt; Time remaining display&lt;li&gt; Large reversible door provides installation flexibility&lt;li&gt; AccelerCare Drying System - safely speeds drying so you can unload and fold before the next load is ready to go in&lt;li&gt; 3 timed cycles&lt;li&gt; 6 automatic cycles&lt;li&gt; Wrinkle Shield Plus Option - automatically tumbles the load without heat to help prevent wrinkles from forming&lt;li&gt; Quiet Dry Plus Noise Reduction&lt;li&gt; Innovative Suspension System&lt;li&gt; Dryer door window&lt;li&gt; Reversible side-swing door&lt;li&gt; Child lockout&lt;li&gt; Dimensions: (HWD) 36 x 27 x 32 7/8 In.", "labels": [[11, 32, "ORG"], [98, 103, "PERSON"], [143, 147, "ORG"], [242, 253, "ORG"], [367, 368, "CARDINAL"], [392, 393, "CARDINAL"], [421, 440, "ORG"], [542, 562, "PRODUCT"], [583, 604, "ORG"], [622, 627, "PERSON"], [687, 692, "WORK_OF_ART"], [724, 727, "ORG"], [729, 731, "CARDINAL"], [739, 745, "CARDINAL"]]}
{"text": "Load capacity: Ultra Capacity Plus 4.0 cu. ft. (IEC equivalent)Spin rating: 1,000 RPM max spin speedWashing Action: Horizontal Tumble Motion With Direct Inject Wash SystemSpeed Controls: 1,000 RPM max spin speedWater controls: Automatic Water Level controlTemperature Options: Care Control Temperature Management, 4 temperature selectionsRinse Options: on/off extra rinse option, rinse and spin optionSpecial feature: Sanitary Cycle and Clean Washer CycleNumber of cycles: 10 factory pre-set cycles and optionsCycles: auto soak, delicate, hand washables, heavy duty, normal/casual, whitest whites, sanitary, clean washer, rinse/spin, variable soak6th Sense technologyStainless steel wash basketBuilt-in water heaterAdd-A-Garment featureAdjustable end-of-cycle signalDelay wash featureDrain/Spin Option3-tray: detergent, bleach, fabric softener dispenser6-point self-le", "labels": [[35, 41, "QUANTITY"], [48, 51, "ORG"], [76, 81, "CARDINAL"], [82, 85, "ORG"], [95, 185, "WORK_OF_ART"], [187, 192, "CARDINAL"], [193, 196, "ORG"], [206, 216, "CARDINAL"], [227, 276, "ORG"], [314, 315, "CARDINAL"], [418, 432, "LOC"], [437, 461, "PRODUCT"], [473, 475, "CARDINAL"], [719, 720, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [777, 807, "ORG"]]}
{"text": "Rated a \"Best Buy\" by a leading consumer magazineENERGY STAR QualifiedUltra Capacity Plus6th Sense TechnologyDirect Inject Wash SystemCare Control Temperature ManagementQuiet Wash Plus Noise ReductionStainless Steel Wash BasketBuilt-In Water Heater10 Factory Pre-Set Cycles and OptionsAdd-A-Garment FeatureAuto Soak CycleClean Washer Cycle with AffreshDelicate CycleHand Wash CycleHeavy Duty CycleNormal/Casual CycleSanitary CycleWhitest Whites CycleAdjustable End-of-Cycle Signal4 Temperature SelectionsDelay WashDeep Clean Steam OptionDrain/Spin OptionOn/Off Extra Rinse OptionRinse and Spin Option3-Tray Detergent, Bleach, Fabric Softener DispenserAutomatic Water Level Control1,000 RPM Maximum Spin Speed6-Point Suspension SystemVariable Speed MotorEasy View Door Window", "labels": [[6, 7, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [22, 23, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [289, 290, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [327, 339, "PERSON"], [345, 360, "ORG"], [392, 404, "ORG"], [589, 606, "ORG"], [618, 660, "ORG"]]}
{"text": "The combination washer and dryer is more energy efficient, and takes up much less space than conventional washer and dryer units. Because this machine is both a washer and a dryer, you never have to transfer loads from one machine to another.", "labels": [[159, 160, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [172, 173, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [219, 222, "CARDINAL"]]}
{"text": "Each drawer doubles as a great place to store laundry products.Provides Easy Access to Front Loading Doors by Raising the Washer and Dryer.Minimizes Bending and Stooping at Doors.Dimensions: (HWD) 13 3/5 x 27 x 28 2/5 In.", "labels": [[23, 24, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [63, 83, "ORG"], [87, 106, "ORG"], [133, 138, "PERSON"], [139, 156, "PERSON"], [161, 178, "ORG"], [192, 195, "ORG"], [197, 203, "CARDINAL"], [206, 208, "CARDINAL"], [211, 217, "CARDINAL"]]}
{"text": "mfr: LG LG 4.2 CF STEAM WASHER REAR PANEL GRAY4.2 cu ft Front Load WasherReturn Policy: Conditional.Dimensions: 27 x 44 x 29.5Color: GRAYWarranty: 1 yearThis item cannot ship to APO/FPO addresses.  Please accept our apologies.", "labels": [[5, 7, "BRAND"], [8, 10, "BRAND"], [112, 114, "CARDINAL"], [117, 119, "CARDINAL"], [133, 145, "CARDINAL"], [147, 148, "CARDINAL"], [178, 185, "ORG"]]}
{"text": "27\" SmartLoad Electric Dryer with 6.2 cu. ft. Capacity, 5 Drying Cycles, Reverse Tumbling and Autosensing", "labels": [[0, 2, "CARDINAL"], [4, 28, "ORG"], [34, 40, "QUANTITY"], [56, 57, "CARDINAL"], [94, 105, "GPE"]]}
{"text": "24\" Front Load Axxis Washer with LED Display - WAS24460UC", "labels": [[0, 2, "CARDINAL"]]}
{"text": "7.0 cu. ft. super capacity  Handles large-size items and family-size loadsSensor Dry Plus  Continually monitors moisture levels to help clothes look better longerRotary electronic controls with cycle countdown display and LED indicators  Simplify the cycle selection and provide accurate cycle timesInterior Dryer Light  Lets you see everything inside for easy loading and unloadingDeluxe Quiet  Provides near-silent performance with a quiet-engineered motor and components, plus an extra layer of insulationAdjustable end-of-cycle signal  Alerts you when cycle is done, saving time between loadsControl TypeRotary-ElectronicCustom Cycles: 1Cycle Countdown: LEDCycle Status LightsHeat Selections: 5Moisture SensorSensor Dry PlusNumber of Cycles: MultipleSpeed DryDrum Interior: DuraDrumDual ThermistorsCottons CycleDelicates CycleDewrinkleEasy Care CycleExtended TumbleMixed Load CycleOptional Dryness Levels - DampOptional Dryness Levels - DryOptional Dryness Levels - Less DryOptional Dryness Levels - More DrySpecialty Cycles: Active WearTimed DryTimed Dry - Actual Minutes on Timer: 90Add TimeAntibacterialQuick Fluff (no heat)Damp Dry SignalDelay Start: up to 18 hoursDryer Interior LightDryer RackDeluxeEnd-of-Cycle SignalAdjustableRemovable Up-Front Lint Filter with reminder lightDoor Style: See-Thru GlassExhaust Options: 4-Way (Rear; Right; Left & Bottom)Flexible Installation: Side-by-Side, Pedestal, StackedFront ServiceableFuel Type: ElectricReverse-a-DoorADA CompliantDimensions: (HDW) 41 1/2 in x 31 1/8 in x 27 in", "labels": [[0, 6, "QUANTITY"], [156, 168, "GPE"], [294, 319, "ORG"], [373, 394, "WORK_OF_ART"], [434, 435, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [498, 518, "ORG"], [591, 638, "ORG"], [707, 744, "PRODUCT"], [746, 776, "ORG"], [791, 824, "ORG"], [924, 969, "PERSON"], [1009, 1029, "ORG"], [1087, 1092, "CARDINAL"], [1165, 1167, "CARDINAL"], [1447, 1462, "ORG"], [1463, 1464, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [1473, 1492, "ORG"], [1495, 1498, "ORG"], [1500, 1506, "CARDINAL"], [1512, 1518, "CARDINAL"], [1524, 1526, "CARDINAL"]]}
{"text": "A new innovation from Haier is solving the problems of apartment dwellers and homeowners alike. The Haier Electric 2.6 Cu. Ft. 115 Volt Portable Dryer (model: HLP140E) compact dryer is powerful but takes up absolutely no floor space. Instead, it is a moun", "labels": [[0, 1, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [22, 27, "BRAND"], [100, 105, "BRAND"], [115, 121, "QUANTITY"], [127, 130, "CARDINAL"], [131, 150, "WORK_OF_ART"], [249, 250, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"]]}
{"text": "Get your laundry extra clean with the power of steam. LGs Front Load Washers use steam in the wash cycle for better washing performance and higher water and energy efficiency. A separate SteamFresh cycle lets you get rid of wrinkles and refresh your clothes anytime.", "labels": [[58, 76, "ORG"], [176, 177, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [187, 197, "ORG"]]}
{"text": "Dishwashers", "labels": []}
{"text": "Naturally steam out wrinkles and odors with the push of a button. Two steam cycles, Quick Refresh and Enhanced Touch-Up, take clothes from lying there to ready-to-wear in as little as 15 minutes. Plus, the Cabrio Steam dryer uses a 'Y' connector, the industry's first direct water installation method. Now, there's no need to manually add water at the start of every steam cycle.7.0 Cu. Ft. Capacity7 Cycles2 Steam CyclesQuick Refresh - Relaxes Wrinkles and Removes Odors from 1 to 5 Garments in as Little as 15 MinutesEnhanced Touch Up - Infuses Clothing with Temperature and Time - from 15 to 40 Minutes - That You ControlDirect Water Installation Method - Y-Connector Taps Directly into Current Water LineDelicate CycleHeavy Duty CycleTimed DryingWindow DoorAccelerCare Drying System5 Drying TemperaturesWrinkle Shield Plus Feature (90 Minutes)3-Way VentingAdjustable End-of-Cycle SignalInterior Drum LightTop-Mounted Lint ScreenWide-Opening Side-Swing DoorUltra Quiet Dry Noise Reduction SystemOptional Laundry TowerCabrio Fabric Care System with Steam DryerDepth: 29 1/4 InchesHeight: 42 InchesWidth: 29 Inches", "labels": [[56, 57, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [66, 69, "CARDINAL"], [84, 119, "ORG"], [171, 194, "TIME"], [206, 218, "ORG"], [230, 231, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [262, 267, "ORDINAL"], [477, 478, "CARDINAL"], [482, 483, "CARDINAL"], [509, 511, "CARDINAL"], [589, 605, "TIME"], [733, 756, "ORG"], [780, 787, "ORG"], [836, 838, "CARDINAL"], [1069, 1075, "CARDINAL"], [1076, 1088, "ORG"], [1090, 1092, "CARDINAL"], [1093, 1104, "ORG"], [1106, 1115, "QUANTITY"]]}
{"text": "Whirlpool WED7500VW Electric Dryer WED7500VW Portable Washer and Dryer", "labels": [[0, 9, "BRAND"]]}
{"text": "Whirlpool WFC7500VW Front-Load Washer WFC7500VW Portable Washer and Dryer", "labels": [[0, 9, "BRAND"], [20, 37, "ORG"], [48, 63, "ORG"]]}
{"text": "27\" Front-Load Washer with 3.8 cu. ft. Capacity, 24 Wash Cycles, HydroWash System, 1,000 RPM Spin Speed and ADA Compliant", "labels": [[0, 2, "CARDINAL"], [4, 21, "ORG"], [27, 33, "QUANTITY"], [49, 51, "CARDINAL"], [83, 88, "CARDINAL"], [89, 103, "ORG"]]}
{"text": "This Front Load Steam Washer features Diamond Drum, Silvercare, 1300 RPM, E-Star. Stainless Platinum Surface, 4. 5 cu ft VRT. The Samsung washer measures 32 inchD x 27 inchW x 39 inchH.", "labels": [[5, 28, "ORG"], [38, 50, "GPE"], [52, 62, "ORG"], [64, 68, "CARDINAL"], [69, 72, "ORG"], [74, 75, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [110, 111, "CARDINAL"], [113, 114, "CARDINAL"], [130, 137, "BRAND"], [154, 156, "CARDINAL"], [165, 167, "CARDINAL"], [168, 173, "ORG"], [176, 178, "CARDINAL"]]}
{"text": "Your laundry room wouldn't be complete without a SAMSUNG DV328 super-capacity dryer. Loaded with convenience features such as sensor drying, wrinkle prevention and reversible door, it's the perfect mate for SAMSUNG's WF328 washer in both performance and style.", "labels": [[47, 48, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [49, 56, "BRAND"], [207, 214, "BRAND"], [217, 222, "GPE"]]}
{"text": "Frigidaire Electric Dryer 5.8 Cubic Foot Super Capacity Drum - FEQ1442BK Features: 5.8 Cu.Ft. Super Capacity Drum 7 Auto Dry Cycles 4 Dryness Level Selections 90 Minute Timed Dry Control Lock Cycle Status Lights Precision Dry Moisture Sensor Timed Dry Cycles Tumble Care Drying System Auto Press Saver Option 4 Temperature Options: High Heat, Medium Heat, Low Heat, No Heat On / Off End-of-Cycle Signal Interior Drum Light Reversible Door Clean Lint Filter Indicator Quick-Clean Lint Screen Installation Options Freestanding Hidden (In Closet) Pedestal Stacked Under-Counter Dimensions: Depth: 28-1/2\" Height: 36\" Width: 27\" Warranty Information: Manufacturer Warranty (authorized online retailer): Full One Year Warranty", "labels": [[0, 10, "BRAND"], [83, 89, "QUANTITY"], [159, 168, "TIME"], [309, 310, "CARDINAL"], [594, 596, "CARDINAL"], [610, 612, "CARDINAL"], [621, 623, "CARDINAL"], [625, 646, "WORK_OF_ART"]]}
{"text": "This Electric Front Load Super Cap Dryer features Steam Drying Technology, Stainless Drum, 11 Preset Cycles, Drying Rack. Stainless Steel Platinum Surface, 7. 4 cu ft. The Samsung dryer measures 31 1/4 inchD x 27 inchW x 39 inchH.", "labels": [[0, 40, "ORG"], [50, 73, "ORG"], [75, 89, "ORG"], [91, 93, "CARDINAL"], [94, 120, "ORG"], [122, 154, "ORG"], [156, 157, "DATE"], [159, 166, "QUANTITY"], [172, 179, "BRAND"], [195, 197, "CARDINAL"], [198, 201, "CARDINAL"], [210, 212, "CARDINAL"], [213, 218, "ORG"], [221, 223, "CARDINAL"]]}
{"text": "This Front Load Steam Washer features Diamond Drum, Silvercare, 1300 RPM, E-Star. Neat White Surface, 4. 5 cu ft VRT. The Samsung washer measures 32 inchD x 27 inchW x 39 inchH.", "labels": [[5, 28, "ORG"], [38, 50, "GPE"], [52, 62, "ORG"], [64, 68, "CARDINAL"], [69, 72, "ORG"], [74, 75, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [102, 103, "CARDINAL"], [105, 106, "CARDINAL"], [122, 129, "BRAND"], [146, 148, "CARDINAL"], [157, 159, "CARDINAL"], [160, 165, "ORG"], [168, 170, "CARDINAL"]]}
{"text": "This Gas Front Load Super Cap Dryer features Steam Drying Technology, Stainless Drum, 11 Preset Cycles, Drying Rack. Stainless Steel Platinum Surface, 7. 4 cu ft. The Samsung dryer measures 31 1/4 inchD x 27 inchW x 39 inchH.", "labels": [[0, 35, "ORG"], [45, 68, "ORG"], [70, 84, "ORG"], [86, 88, "CARDINAL"], [89, 115, "ORG"], [117, 149, "ORG"], [151, 152, "DATE"], [154, 161, "QUANTITY"], [167, 174, "BRAND"], [190, 192, "CARDINAL"], [193, 196, "CARDINAL"], [205, 207, "CARDINAL"], [208, 213, "ORG"], [216, 218, "CARDINAL"]]}
{"text": "This Front Load Steam Washer features Diamond Drum, VRT, Silvercare, 1200 RPM, E-Star. Neat White Surface, 4. 0 cu ft. The Samsung washer measures 31 inchD x 27 inchW x 38 inchH.", "labels": [[5, 28, "ORG"], [38, 50, "GPE"], [52, 55, "ORG"], [57, 67, "ORG"], [69, 73, "CARDINAL"], [74, 77, "ORG"], [79, 80, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [107, 108, "CARDINAL"], [123, 130, "BRAND"], [147, 149, "CARDINAL"], [158, 160, "CARDINAL"], [161, 166, "ORG"], [169, 171, "CARDINAL"], [172, 178, "WORK_OF_ART"]]}
{"text": "Allergiene(TM) Allergiene(TM) cycle is proven to reduce certain allergens such as house dust mites and domestic animal dander. SteamFresh(TM) LG's innovative SteamFresh(TM) cycle makes it possible for you to refresh and reduce wrinkles in up to 5 garments at one time. Running late for work with no time to iron? Load a cotton blend shirt into the SteamWasher(TM) and select the SteamFresh(TM) cycle. You'll be ready to go in just 20 minutes. Ultra Capacity with NeveRust(TM) Stainless Steel Drum One of the largest capacity front-load washers for the consumer market which means fewer loads, easy handling of large comforters and better water and energy efficiency. Direct Drive Motor Power is delivered right to the drum from the motor without belts, resulting in a highly durable, powerful and quiet washing machine. Electronic Control Panel with Dial-A-Cycle(TM)", "labels": [[142, 144, "BRAND"], [245, 246, "CARDINAL"], [318, 319, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [348, 362, "ORG"], [426, 441, "TIME"], [443, 457, "ORG"], [463, 475, "ORG"], [497, 500, "CARDINAL"], [667, 691, "ORG"], [766, 767, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [820, 844, "ORG"], [855, 856, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"]]}
{"text": "Whirlpool WED9300VU 27 Inch Electric Dryer with 7 cu ft Capacity 7 Cycles", "labels": [[0, 9, "BRAND"], [10, 42, "MONEY"], [48, 52, "QUANTITY"]]}
{"text": "ENERGY STAR Qualified Meets or exceeds federal guidelines for energy efficiency, which means year-round energy and money savingsSmartDispense Technology SmartDispense* pedestal holds up to 6 months of detergent and 95 ounces of fabric softener** and dispenses the right amount, at the right timeH2ition Wash System This intuitive clothes care technology automatically senses the size of load to add the right amount of water at the right temperature to save energy*** and water and experience a terrific cleanCleanSpeak Communication System The washer communicates electronically with the dryer, which then presets dry cycles for better clothes care, increased time savings and greater convenienceStain Inspector System Treats over 40 common stains depending on model, from grass stains to grease; It is the best stain removal system availableSpecialty Wash Cycles Ensure that your expensive fabrics get the special attention they deserve", "labels": [[22, 27, "PERSON"], [93, 97, "DATE"], [142, 166, "ORG"], [183, 197, "DATE"], [215, 224, "QUANTITY"], [493, 494, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [686, 726, "ORG"], [732, 734, "CARDINAL"], [853, 871, "ORG"]]}
{"text": "27\" Front-Load Washer with 4.0 cu. ft. Capacity, 12 Wash Cycles, 7 Options, 5 Temperature Settings, 1200 RPM Spin Speed, SilverCare/VRT Technology and Diamond Drum Design: Tango Red", "labels": [[0, 2, "CARDINAL"], [4, 21, "ORG"], [27, 33, "QUANTITY"], [49, 51, "CARDINAL"], [52, 63, "ORG"], [65, 66, "CARDINAL"], [76, 77, "CARDINAL"], [100, 104, "CARDINAL"], [105, 119, "ORG"], [121, 131, "ORG"], [151, 181, "ORG"]]}
{"text": "Malber(R) is a worldwide company whose products are distributed on every continent. The manufacturing plant, located in Italy, comprises approximately 1,000,000 square feet and is a state-of-the-art facility producing 11,000 units a day. The owners of Malber USA have been in the appliance industry since 1933. In 1988, seeing a need for these space-saving washers and dryers, Malber USA introduced them into the NY, NJ, and CT market. Today, Malber USA distributes its line of residential laundry machines throughout the United States. Over 20,000 machines are currently in use in the United States. Malber owners come from all walks of life, from the new mother living in an apartment, to the elderly who find it difficult to walk with heavy baskets of laundry, to the apartment dweller who simply doesn't have the time to spend waiting in the laundry room or in laundromats.", "labels": [[13, 14, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [120, 125, "GPE"], [137, 172, "QUANTITY"], [180, 181, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [218, 224, "CARDINAL"], [231, 232, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [252, 262, "ORG"], [305, 309, "DATE"], [314, 318, "DATE"], [327, 328, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [377, 387, "ORG"], [413, 415, "GPE"], [417, 419, "GPE"], [425, 427, "ORG"], [436, 441, "DATE"], [443, 453, "ORG"], [518, 535, "GPE"], [537, 548, "CARDINAL"], [582, 599, "GPE"], [601, 607, "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "Genuine Whirlpool-Maytag Part # 6-3037050. Belt Pulley Tension Used On Maytag Dryers. Also Used On Kenmore Elite Models, Whirlpool Models And Also Maytag Models.", "labels": [[8, 17, "BRAND"], [18, 24, "BRAND"], [30, 41, "MONEY"], [43, 70, "ORG"], [71, 77, "BRAND"], [99, 106, "BRAND"], [121, 130, "BRAND"], [147, 153, "BRAND"]]}
{"text": "27\" Steam Washer/Dryer Combo with 4.2 cu. ft. Capacity, 9 Wash &amp; 5 Dry Programs, Spin Speed of 1320 RPMs and Allergiene Cycle", "labels": [[0, 2, "CARDINAL"], [4, 28, "ORG"], [34, 40, "QUANTITY"], [56, 57, "CARDINAL"], [58, 64, "ORG"], [69, 70, "CARDINAL"], [71, 83, "ORG"], [85, 95, "PRODUCT"], [99, 103, "DATE"], [113, 129, "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "This Gas Front Load Super Cap Dryer features Sensor Drying, Stainless Steel Drum, 7 Presets, Rack. Breakwater Blue Surface, 7. 3 cu ft. The Samsung dryer measures 30 1/4 foot D x 27 inchW x 38 11/16 foot H.", "labels": [[0, 35, "ORG"], [45, 58, "ORG"], [60, 80, "ORG"], [82, 83, "CARDINAL"], [84, 91, "ORG"], [93, 97, "ORG"], [99, 122, "PRODUCT"], [124, 125, "CARDINAL"], [127, 134, "QUANTITY"], [140, 147, "BRAND"], [163, 174, "QUANTITY"], [175, 176, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [179, 181, "CARDINAL"], [190, 203, "QUANTITY"]]}
{"text": "This Front Load Steam Washer features VRT, 1100 RPM, E-Star. Breakwater Blue Surface, 4. 0 cu ft. The Samsung washer measures 31 inchD x 27 inchW x 38 inchH.", "labels": [[5, 28, "ORG"], [38, 41, "ORG"], [43, 47, "CARDINAL"], [48, 51, "ORG"], [53, 54, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [86, 87, "CARDINAL"], [102, 109, "BRAND"], [126, 128, "CARDINAL"], [137, 139, "CARDINAL"], [140, 145, "ORG"], [148, 150, "CARDINAL"], [151, 157, "WORK_OF_ART"]]}
{"text": "This Front Load Steam Washer features VRT, 1100 RPM, E-Star. Neat White Surface, 4. 0 cu ft. The Samsung washer measures 31 inchD x 27 inchW x 38 inchH.", "labels": [[5, 28, "ORG"], [38, 41, "ORG"], [43, 47, "CARDINAL"], [48, 51, "ORG"], [53, 54, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [81, 82, "CARDINAL"], [97, 104, "BRAND"], [121, 123, "CARDINAL"], [132, 134, "CARDINAL"], [135, 140, "ORG"], [143, 145, "CARDINAL"], [146, 152, "WORK_OF_ART"]]}
{"text": "15.5\" pedestal doubles as a storage drawerconvenient sliding shelf to support your laundry basket", "labels": [[0, 4, "CARDINAL"], [26, 27, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"]]}
{"text": "A stylish Amana gas dryer is the perfect tonic for a tired laundry room. Not only can you dry more at a time in this 6.5 cu. ft. Super Capacity dryer, but loading and unloading is quick and easy with a wide-opening, side-swing door. Automatic Dryness Control means you don't have to worry about overdrying. Plus, the Wrinkle Prevent option puts a stop to wrinkles for those times you can't get there just as the end-of-cycle signal sounds.", "labels": [[0, 1, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [10, 15, "BRAND"], [51, 52, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [102, 103, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [117, 123, "QUANTITY"], [129, 143, "ORG"], [200, 201, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [233, 258, "ORG"], [317, 324, "ORG"], [345, 346, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"]]}
{"text": "Upgrade your laundry room with a stylish Amana electric dryer. With a 6.5 cu. ft. Super Capacity you can dry more at a time so you'll spend less time doing laundry. A total of 7 cycles and 3 temperature settings provide a variety of drying options for your clothes. The Wrinkle Prevent option tumbles clothes without heat once the cycle is finished to help keep wrinkles from setting in. Also, Automatic Dryness Control monitors the drying temperature so you don't have to worry about overdrying.", "labels": [[31, 32, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [41, 46, "BRAND"], [68, 69, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [70, 76, "QUANTITY"], [82, 96, "ORG"], [117, 118, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [165, 166, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [176, 177, "CARDINAL"], [189, 190, "CARDINAL"], [220, 221, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [270, 277, "ORG"], [394, 419, "ORG"]]}
{"text": "Upgrade your laundry room with a stylish Amana gas dryer. With a 6.5 cu. ft. Super Capacity you can dry more at a time so you'll spend less time doing laundry. A total of 7 cycles and 3 temperature settings provide a variety of drying options for your clothes. The Wrinkle Prevent option tumbles clothes without heat once the cycle is finished to help keep wrinkles from setting in. Also, Automatic Dryness Control monitors the drying temperature so you don't have to worry about overdrying.", "labels": [[31, 32, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [41, 46, "BRAND"], [63, 64, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [65, 71, "QUANTITY"], [77, 91, "ORG"], [112, 113, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [160, 161, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [171, 172, "CARDINAL"], [184, 185, "CARDINAL"], [215, 216, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [265, 272, "ORG"], [389, 414, "ORG"]]}
{"text": "Freshen up your laundry room with a stylish new Amana washer. Antimicrobial component protection adds an extra shot of refreshment. Built into the tub ring, it helps prevent the growth of stain- and odor-causing bacteria. A 3.2 cu. ft. capacity means you can clean more at a time. And, with 9 cycles and 4 water levels there's sure to be a combination to match your cleaning needs. What's more, the Automatic Temperature Control helps protect your fabrics by adjusting the incoming water flow to maintain the selected water temperature.", "labels": [[34, 35, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [48, 53, "BRAND"], [222, 223, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [224, 230, "QUANTITY"], [273, 274, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [291, 292, "CARDINAL"], [304, 305, "CARDINAL"], [338, 339, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [395, 428, "ORG"]]}
{"text": "Liven up laundry day with a stylish Amana washer. Antimicrobial component protection built into the tub ring helps this washer keep it clean by preventing the growth of stain- and odor-causing bacteria. The 3.2 cu. ft. Super Capacity provides plenty of space for your cleaning needs. This washer offers 14 cycles and 5 water levels to help you care for a wide variety of fabrics. Plus, this model features bleach and fabric softener dispensers so you can load it up and not worry about adding them at the right time", "labels": [[26, 27, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [36, 41, "BRAND"], [207, 213, "QUANTITY"], [219, 233, "ORG"], [303, 305, "CARDINAL"], [317, 318, "CARDINAL"], [353, 354, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"]]}
{"text": "", "labels": []}
{"text": "ENERGY STAR Qualified Meets or exceeds federal guidelines for energy efficiency for year-round energy to help save money4.1 IEC cu. ft. colossal capacity stainless steel basket Colossal size stainless steel drum can handle family-size loadsHydroWave system with Infusor Advanced wash action provides gentle, thorough cleaning700 RPM spin speed Fast speeds remove more water during the spin cycle to minimize drying time5 wash/spin speed combinations Washer alternates speeds for great clothes careRainShower rinse system This system uses less water than traditional toploads, and provides clean rinse performance similar to a frontload washer rinse system", "labels": [[22, 27, "PERSON"], [84, 94, "DATE"], [115, 123, "PERSON"], [124, 127, "ORG"], [177, 185, "PRODUCT"], [262, 278, "ORG"], [329, 332, "ORG"], [450, 456, "ORG"], [624, 625, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"]]}
{"text": "Together, Whirlpool and Maytag emerge a more compelling company positioned to deliver the most innovative portfolio of products and services to consumers throughout the world. Together, they will continue to find new ways to delight consumers while striving to fulfill their vision of Every Home . . . Everywhere with Pride, Passion and Performance.The Sensi-Care wash system of this high-efficiency front load washer offers outstanding cleaning performance. Plus, the Smooth Balance suspension system helps reduce vibration and noise, allowing it to be installed virtually anywhere. Features the MaxExtract option that accelerates the last 30 seconds of the final spin to remove moisture and reduce drying times.Maytag Commercial TechnologySteamClean OptionSteam Sanitization CyclesSuperSize Capacity PlusSmooth Balance Suspension SystemMaxExtract Extended Spin OptionSensi-Care Wash SystemEnergy Star Qualified, CEE Tier I", "labels": [[10, 19, "BRAND"], [24, 30, "BRAND"], [38, 39, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [285, 295, "ORG"], [353, 363, "ORG"], [597, 607, "PERSON"], [632, 651, "TIME"], [713, 719, "BRAND"], [752, 801, "ORG"], [914, 922, "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "Performance Series Gas Dryer with Steam-Enhanced CycleWith the revitalizing power of steam, you can pull a shirt right from the dryer that smells fresh, looks great, and is ready to wear. A Steam-Enhanced cycle relaxes wrinkles while helping to remove odors. Select from nine cycles and five temperatures, including an NSF Certified Sanitary cycle, to help eliminate bacteria on important items like pillows and teddy bears. In this 7.2 cu. ft. Performance Series gas dryer, you get the power you expect from Maytag &reg; Commercial Technology, long-lasting commercial-grade components, and the GentleBreeze drying system with IntelliDry &reg; moisture sensor. And the QuietSeries 300 sound package and Smooth Balance suspension system help keep things quiet.", "labels": [[0, 28, "ORG"], [34, 58, "ORG"], [105, 106, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [188, 189, "ENERGY_EFFICIENCY"], [190, 204, "ORG"], [271, 275, "CARDINAL"], [287, 291, "CARDINAL"], [433, 439, "QUANTITY"], [457, 463, "EVENT"], [509, 515, "BRAND"], [522, 543, "ORG"], [595, 607, "ORG"], [627, 642, "ORG"], [703, 717, "ORG"]]}
{"text": "LG Red wild Cherry 4.5 Steam Dryer", "labels": [[0, 2, "BRAND"], [12, 34, "ORG"]]}
{"text": "7.0 cu. ft. Performance Series Front Load Electric Steam Dryer - MEDE500V", "labels": [[0, 6, "QUANTITY"]]}
